<?xml version="1.0"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="cards.xslt"?>

<deck>
	<deckname>Boat Graveyard</deckname>
	<version>2.0</version>
	<card>
		<name>Unstable Footing</name>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<text><p>Reduce all damage dealt by 1.</p><p>At the end of their turn a player may discard 2 cards to destroy this card</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>Ragged edges of rusty sheet metal waited under every step I took, scraping and stabbing against the soles of my costumed feet.</text>
			<source>Prey 14.11</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Rusted Hulk</name>
		<hp>15</hp>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<text>Whenever damage would be dealt to all targets or all targets of a particular type, this target takes one instance of the damage and prevents the rest of it</text>
		<quote>
			<text>...forty or fifty derelict ships, some bigger in sheer mass than the skyscrapers downtown</text>
			<source>Prey 14.11</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Aquatic Environment</name>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<text><p>All effects that would occur at the end of a turn occur at the start of the turn instead.</p><p>If a hero plays a card they cannot use a power that turn, and vice-versa.</p><p>At the start of the environment turn, a player may discard their hand to destroy this card</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>The floor sloped one way. Half of the room was metal flooring covered in sand, the lowest half was submerged.</text>
			<source>Prey 14.11</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Cold and Unpleasant</name>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<text><p>At the start of the environment turn, all targets take 1 cold damage.</p><p>At the start of their turn, a hero may skip the rest of their turn to destroy this card</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>...the Boat Graveyard - an entire section of the coastline where boats had sat for so long that they'd rusted or taken on water.</text>
			<source>Prey 14.11</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Useful Cache</name>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<text>When this card is destroyed, a hero may draw 3 cards</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"...I'll use my bugs to mark out the traps that Bonesaw set up inside."</text>
			<source>Skitter, Prey 14.11</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Smugglers</name>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<hp>5</hp>
		<text>At the end of the environment turn, this card destroys 1 hero card in play</text>
		<quote>
			<text>Police had made arrests, but actually moving the ships out of the way required sailors, and the move had mobilized enough of them that clearing the upper areas of the docks of the ships became all but impossible.</text>
			<source>Prey 14.11</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Sound Carries</name>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<text><p>Whenever a target is put into play, play the top card of the environment deck.</p><p>At the end of the environment turn, a hero may discard 2 cards to destroy this card</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>"...She knows where we are."</text>
			<source>Tattletale, Prey 14.11</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
</deck>