<?xml version="1.0"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="cards.xslt"?>

<environment
xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xmlns="http://www.jamespicone.name/parahumans"
xs:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../hero.xsd">
	<name>Coil's Base</name>
	<version>2.0.0</version>
	<textcolour>black</textcolour>
	<cardcolour>white</cardcolour>
	<boxcolour>white</boxcolour>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<name>Blast Doors</name>
		<type>Structure</type>
		<hp>10</hp>
		<text><p>Reduce all fire and projectile damage by 2.</p><p>At the start of their turn, a hero may skip the rest of their turn to destroy this card</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>"A column, with the panic room dead center. When they retreated inside, they pulled the switch, and the entire substructure dropped two thousand, five hundred feet below ground, putting the upper end of the column between us and them."</text>
			<source>Satyrical, Venom 29.6</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<name>Ablative Cladding</name>
		<type>Structure</type>
		<hp>10</hp>
		<text><p>Reduce all toxic and melee damage by 2.</p><p>At the start of their turn, a hero may skip the rest of their turn to destroy this card</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>The laser didn't cut the armor. It was capable of cutting granite like a hot knife through butter, but it didn't cut the armor.</text>
			<source>Interlude 23</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<name>Earthing</name>
		<type>Structure</type>
		<hp>10</hp>
		<text><p>Reduce all cold and lightning damage by 2.</p><p>At the start of their turn, a hero may skip the rest of their turn to destroy this card</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>Another lightning strike, curving in the air, hit the hand. Residual electricity danced between the two extended fingers.

It was working, and as much as it was a success in helping against the lightning, it was working to help morale. To contribute something, anything, it mattered.</text>
			<source>Crushed 24.1</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<name>Pinned Down</name>
		<text><p>Heroes cannot play Ongoing or Equipment cards.</p><p>At the start of their turn, a hero may skip the rest of their turn to destroy this card</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>"I've invested a great deal of time and money into establishing your two groups here in Brockton Bay, and I did it for precisely this sort of scenario. Again, the timing is unfortunate, but I still expect you to address this situation. You'll want to verify whether Bitch, Ballistic and Genesis are captured or simply pinned down somewhere, rescue them if need be and dispatch Dragon."</text>
			<source>Coil, Monarch 16.1</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<name>Sealed Chamber</name>
		<type>Structure</type>
		<hp>20</hp>
		<text><p>If this card is destroyed, the heroes lose the game.</p><p>At the start of their turn, a hero may skip the rest of their turn. If they do, this structure regains 5 HP</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>"On a scale of one to ten," I asked, "Just how bad is this?"

"Let me answer your question with another question," Tattletale said. "You think we could convince the PRT to turn on the air raid sirens?"</text>
			<source>Skitter, Monarch 16.13</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<name>Trapped Chamber</name>
		<type>Structure</type>
		<hp>14</hp>
		<text><p>Heroes cannot use powers.</p><p>At the start of their turn, a hero may skip the rest of their turn to destroy this card</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>A series of barely-audible 'beeps' sounded throughout the room. What had I just disabled? Claymores?

Did I really want to know?</text>
			<source>Imago 21.7</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<name>Cover</name>
		<type>Structure</type>
		<hp>8</hp>
		<text><p>Whenever a target would be damaged, redirect that damage to this card.</p><p>Reduce damage dealt to this target by 1</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>I looked at the others, and they were all moving into cover. Kaiser, Fenja and Menja had all ducked into an alleyway. Bitch and her dogs were disappearing around the far corner of the same building, making only the scratching noise of claws against concrete.</text>
			<source>Hive 5.6</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<name>Repair Crew</name>
		<hp>5</hp>
		<text>At the end of the environment turn, all structures regain 3 HP</text>
		<quote>
			<text>To outside observers, Creep was an ordinary laborer driving an electrician's van to the construction site.</text>
			<source>Interlude 8</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Mercenaries</name>
		<hp>6</hp>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<text>At the end of the environment turn, this card deals H - 1 energy damage to the two targets with the highest HP</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"Either way, you forgot the cardinal rule of employing mercenaries. They follow the person with the money."</text>
			<source>Tattletale, Monarch 16.13</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Construction Work</name>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<text>At the end of the environnment turn, reveal cards from the top of the environment environment until you reveal three Structure cards. Put them into play and shuffle the other revealed cards back into the environment. Then, destroy this card</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"And the containment facility?" he asked, though he already knew the answer, from the interruptions while he spent the night in the facility. He'd heard the noise of the work just hours ago, been informed that people were arriving.</text>
			<source>Coil, Interlude 8</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Laser Rifles</name>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<text>Increase damage dealt by Villain targets by 1. Change all villain target damage to Energy</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"These guys? They've got these lasers hooked up to the machine guns they carry around. If they don't think bullets are doing it, or if they're after people who are behind cover, they fire off these purple laser beams that can cut through steel."</text>
			<source>Thug, Interlude 2</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Stranger and Master Protocols</name>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<text><p>Heroes cannot cause other heroes to draw cards, search their environment, regain HP, use a power, or play a card</p><p>At the start of their turn, a player may skip the rest of their turn to destroy this card</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>"This is what hell is like," Revel said. "Listen to me."</text>
			<source>Revel, Sting 26.1</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
</environment>