<?xml version="1.0"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="cards.xslt"?>

<environment
xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xmlns="http://www.jamespicone.name/parahumans"
xs:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../hero.xsd">
	<name>Kyushu</name>
	<version>2.0.2</version>
	<textcolour>black</textcolour>
	<cardcolour>white</cardcolour>
	<boxcolour>white</boxcolour>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<name>Black Kaze</name>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>6</hp>
		<text>
			<p>At the end of the environment turn, move this card next to the character card target with the lowest HP other than the one it is currently next to. Then, Black Kaze deals 3 irreducible melee damage to the target they are next to</p>
			<p>The first time Black Kaze would be damaged each round, redirect the damage to the target Black Kaze is next to</p>
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>Nobody knew her real body count, but conservative estimates put it in the tens of thousands. She'd roamed the remains of the landscape, killing survivors, killing rescuers, boarding the ships that approached too close to the ruined area and killing the crews, and rendering a widespread area devoid of life.</text>
			<source>Extinction 27.3</source>
		</quote>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<name>Lung</name>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>12</hp>
		<text>
			<p>At the end of the environment turn, Lung deals 3 fire damage to all targets other than Lung.</p>
			<p>At the start of the environment turn, Lung regains 2 HP</p>
			<p>Reduce damage dealt to Lung by 1</p>
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>Lung roared, burned head to toe as he clawed deeper still. If Leviathan's muscle was as hard as steel, Lung would burn hot enough to melt steel.</text>
			<source>Interlude 22</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<hp>4</hp>
		<name>Sentai Elite</name>
		<text>
			At the end of the environment turn, this card deals X energy damage to the non-environment target with the highest HP, where X = 2 * the number of Sentai Elite cards in play
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>Leviathan couldn't attack from range, and couldn't get close without getting pummelled. He attempted to run, only for Japan's foremost team, the Sentai Elite, to step into his way, blocking his progress.</text>
			<source>Interlude 22</source>
		</quote>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<name>Slide Into the Sea</name>
		<text>
			<p>
				At the end of the environment turn:
				<ul>
					<li>Play the top card of the environment environment, then</li>
					<li>Shuffle the top 2 cards of the environment trash back into the environment environment, then</li>
					<li>Remove the top card of the environment environment from the game</li>
				</ul>
			</p>
			
			<p>At the start of the environment turn, if there are no cards left in the environment environment, the heroes lose the game</p>
			<p>When this card would be destroyed, if there are other environment cards in play, destroy one of them instead</p>
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"May ninth, 2005. Nearly half a million dead. The Canadian island simply gone, after the shelf of land holding it up cracked in the face of what we now understand were incredible pressures beneath the water level."</text>
			<source>Legend, Extermination 8.2</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<name>Only the Indomitable Remain</name>
		<text>
			<p>Reduce all damage dealt by 1</p>
			<p>At the end of the environment turn, all targets regain 1 HP</p>
			<p>When a target is destroyed, destroy this card</p>
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>The only ones left were the indomitable, and for now, Lung was among them.</text>
			<source>Interlude 22</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<name>Parahuman Backup</name>
		<text>
			<p>When this card enters play, all players may draw a card</p>
			<p>At the end of the environment turn, destroy this card</p>
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>A pre-battle speech from Legend. It almost made the lousiest, most painful and dangerous situations I'd put up with since putting on my costume worth it.</text>
			<source>Extermination 8.1</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<name>Fatalism and Despair</name>
		<text>
			<p>When this card enters play, all hero targets deal themselves 2 psychic damage</p>
			<p>At the end of the environment turn, destroy this card</p>
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"You're going to die!" the Sentai in black and yellow shouted.</text>
			<source>Interlude 22</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<name>Collapsing Building</name>
		<text>
			<p>When this card enters play, a player may discard 2 cards. If they do, destroy this card</p>
			<p>At the end of the environment turn, deal 4 irreducible melee damage to the target with the second highest HP, then destroy this card</p>
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text><i>Depart from the rooftops, buildings may come down imminently</i></text>
			<source>Dragon, Extermination 8.3</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<name>Tidal Wave</name>
		<text>
			<p>When this card enters play, this card deals 2 melee damage to all hero targets</p>
			<p>Any hero dealt damage in this way must discard a card</p>
			<p>At the end of the environment turn, destroy this card</p>
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>It was my armband. The screen was ringed by a square of yellow, a yellow triangle with a black exclamation mark pointing in Leviathan's general direction.</text>
			<source>Extermination 8.3</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<!--
	
		Super Sentai
		Black Kaze
		Everything's sinking
		Lung
	
	-->
</environment>