<?xml version="1.0"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="cards.xslt"?>

<deck
xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xmlns="http://www.jamespicone.name/parahumans"
xs:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../hero.xsd">
	<name>Lausanne</name>
	<version>2.0.1</version>
	<textcolour>black</textcolour>
	<cardcolour>white</cardcolour>
	<boxcolour>white</boxcolour>

	<specialcard>
		<name>Citizen</name>
		<front>
			<hp>8</hp>
			<type>Citizen</type>
			<type>Broken</type>
			<text>
				<p>At the end of the Environment turn, this card deals 3 projectile damage to the hero target with the lowest HP</p>
				<p>When this card is flipped to this side destroy 1 hero card</p>
			</text>
			<quote>
				<text>"I'm sure you heard about it, you're not that young. Suicide bombers, dirty bombs. Terrorism, if you will. Eleven year olds and old men making their way to Amsterdam or London and opening fire in a crowded area."</text>
				<source></source>
			</quote>
		</front>
		<back>
			<type>Citizen</type>
			<text>
				<p>This is the back of the card</p>
				<p>When this card would be put into play, put it into play this side up</p>
				<p>At the start of the environment turn, flip this card</p>
				<p>When this card is destroyed, deal 2 psychic damage to all heroes</p>
			</text>
		</back>
	</specialcard>
	
	<specialcard>
		<name>Citizen</name>
		<front>
			<hp>8</hp>
			<type>Citizen</type>
			<text>
				<p>When this card is destroyed, deal 1 psychic damage to all heroes</p>
			</text>
			<quote>
				<text>"It's what happened in... what was that place called? Lausanne? Switzerland. She showed up, and nobody wanted to pick a fight with her, and they were curious, so they studied her, and tried to communicate with her."</text>
				<source>Jess, Migration 17.3</source>
			</quote>
		</front>
		<back>
			<type>Citizen</type>
			<text>
				<p>This is the back of the card</p>
				<p>When this card would be put into play, put it into play this side up</p>
				<p>At the start of the environment turn, flip this card</p>
				<p>When this card is destroyed, deal 2 psychic damage to all heroes</p>
			</text>
		</back>
	</specialcard>

	<specialcard>
		<name>Citizen</name>
		<front>
			<hp>8</hp>
			<type>Citizen</type>
			<text>
				<p>The first time damage would be dealt to a hero target each round, reduce the damage by 1</p>
			</text>
			<quote>
				<text>"Defiant and Dragon wanted to use the hostages against me, putting me in a lose-lose situation where I was caught between them and having to hurt people to try to escape. I think I'm turning the tables, now. We're going to walk out of this school as a group. If you want to stop us, you're going to have to hurt us, and you aren't capable of doing that to people any more than I am."</text>
				<source>Skitter, Chrysalis 20.5</source>
			</quote>
		</front>
		<back>
			<type>Citizen</type>
			<text>
				<p>This is the back of the card</p>
				<p>When this card would be put into play, put it into play this side up</p>
				<p>When damage would be dealt to a hero target, flip this card</p>
				<p>When this card is destroyed, deal 2 psychic damage to all heroes</p>
			</text>
		</back>
	</specialcard>

	<specialcard>
		<name>Citizen</name>
		<front>
			<hp>8</hp>
			<type>Citizen</type>
			<type>Broken</type>
			<text>
				<p>Increase damage dealt to hero targets by 1</p>
				<p>When this card is flipped to this side, destroy all Citizens that aren't also Broken</p>
			</text>
			<quote>
				<text>"...Tons of people gathered. Then she... sang? Screamed? Whatever this is. There was chaos, people didn't know what was happening, so they weren't able to evacuate that well. Roads clogged. And then they started flipping out. Emotions ramped up, inhibitions lowered, flashbacks to old traumas. And a lot of the emotion that got juiced up was fear."</text>
				<source>Jess, Migration 17.3</source>
			</quote>
		</front>
		<back>
			<type>Citizen</type>
			<text>
				<p>This is the back of the card</p>
				<p>When this card would be put into play, put it into play this side up</p>
				<p>When damage would be dealt to a hero target, flip this card</p>
				<p>When this card is destroyed, deal 2 psychic damage to all heroes</p>
			</text>
		</back>
	</specialcard>

	<specialcard>
		<name>Citizen</name>
		<front>
			<hp>8</hp>
			<type>Citizen</type>
			<text>
				<p>The first time each round a hero card enters play, that hero may draw a card</p>
			</text>
			<quote>
				<text>The man who'd helped me with Mannequin had the concrete block in his hand, and for the third time, be brought it down on Mannequin's head. The head came free of the chain and fell to the ground, rolling briefly.</text>
				<source>Plague 12.7</source>
			</quote>
		</front>
		<back>
			<type>Citizen</type>
			<text>
				<p>This is the back of the card</p>
				<p>When this card would be put into play, put it into play this side up</p>
				<p>When a hero card would be put into play, flip this card</p>
				<p>When this card is destroyed, deal 2 psychic damage to all heroes</p>
			</text>
		</back>
	</specialcard>

	<specialcard>
		<name>Citizen</name>
		<front>
			<hp>8</hp>
			<type>Citizen</type>
			<type>Broken</type>
			<text>
				<p>The first time a hero card enters play each turn, that hero discards a card</p>
				<p>When this card is flipped to this side, remove the top card of each hero deck from the game</p>
			</text>
			<quote>
				<text>"It keeps happening. Every time she shows up. Every time, people who've heard this song that's in our head? Things go wrong. They snap, they break, their lives fall apart, or they do something, and it makes something else happen, and there's a major disaster. That guy who was supposedly making a clean energy source that could power whole cities? His wife and kids got killed and he became a supervillain who made it a life goal to murder anyone who tries to better society with their powers."</text>
				<source>Jess, Migration 17.5</source>
			</quote>
		</front>
		<back>
			<type>Citizen</type>
			<text>
				<p>This is the back of the card</p>
				<p>When this card would be put into play, put it into play this side up</p>
				<p>When a hero card would be put into play, flip this card</p>
				<p>When this card is destroyed, deal 2 psychic damage to all heroes</p>
			</text>
		</back>
	</specialcard>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<name>A Strategem Unveiled</name>
		<text>
			<p>When this card is revealed, put it into play</p>
			<p>At the end of the environment turn, take all Citizen cards from the the Environment deck and trash, shuffle them, and put them into play</p>
			<p>When a Citizen card is destroyed, destroy this card</p>
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>
				<p>"How the fuck is she not a tinker!?"</p>
				<p>"She isn't! She's never done anything like this before!"</p>
			</text>
			<source>
				Krouse &amp; Jess, Migration 17.2
			</source>
		</quote>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<name>Hard Decisions</name>
		<text>
			<p>When this card is put into play all heroes must simultaneously and secretly vote for another hero (count down from 3)</p>
			<p>If there is a clear winner, that hero takes 2 psychic damage, and the heroes may destroy a Citizen card in play</p>
			<p>Otherwise, all heroes take 2 psychic damage, then flip all Citizen cards in play</p>
			<p>Then destroy this card</p>
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"Step away from the fence! This area is under quarantine! Seek shelter and wait for further instructions! If you approach or touch the fence, you will be shot!"</text>
			<source>A soldier, Migration 17.2</source>
		</quote>
	</card>

	<specialcard>
		<name>The Simurgh</name>
		
		<front>
			<type>Benevolent Angel?</type>
			<text>
				<p>At the start of the game, put this card into play, this side up</p>
				<p>All environment cards are indestructible</p>
				<p>Citizen cards cannot flip</p>
				<p>Whenever the top card of the Environment deck would be played, instead search the Environment deck for a Citizen card and put it into play</p>
				<p>At the end of the Environment turn, place a Fate token on The Simurgh</p>
				<p>When there are 3 Fate tokens on the Simurgh, flip her</p>
			</text>
			<quote>
				<text>"...When she first showed up, she just appeared and hovered there. Some place in Switzerland. They thought she was like Scion. Maybe someone who got a concentrated dose of whatever gives people powers, maybe someone who was in just the right mental state for a trigger event."</text>
				<source>Jess, Migration 17.2</source>
			</quote>
		</front>
		<back>
			<type>Newest Endbringer</type>
			<hp>14</hp>
			<text>
				<p>When this card is flipped to this side, flip every Citizen card in play</p>
				<p>At the end of the environment turn, deal X psychic damage to every hero, where X is the number of Fate tokens on this card</p>
				<p>When a Citizen card enters play, place a Fate token on this card</p>
			</text>
			<quote>
				<text>"...And when we thought things would be okay, she made a move. The entire population of the city around her, with all the people who had come to talk with her and research her..."</text>
				<source>Jess, Migration 17.2</source>
			</quote>
		</back>
	</specialcard>

	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<name>Hurried Backup</name>
		<text>
			<p>When this card enters play, all heroes draw a card</p>
			<p>When this card is destroyed, all heroes discard a card</p>
			<p>When a hero target is destroyed, destroy this card</p>
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>With a sound like a muffled thunderclap, a half dozen people appeared in the center of the empty lot.</text>
			<source>Extermination 8.1</source>
		</quote>
	</card>

	<card>
		<name>Looters</name>
		<hp>4</hp>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<text>
			<p>At the end of the environment turn, this card deals 1 melee damage to the hero with the most cards in play</p>
			<p>When this card deals damage to a hero, destroy a card owned by that hero</p>
			<p>When this card deals damage to a villain target, destroy a villain non-character card</p>
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>They'd raided countless homes and businesses, taken everything of value they could uncover. Phone lines were down everywhere, police response times far slower with the roads in the condition they were. The looters had amassed a small fortune in stolen possessions</text>
			<source>Parasite 10.2</source>
		</quote>
	</card>

	<card>
		<name>General Armstrong</name>
		<hp>8</hp>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<text>
			<p>At the end of the environment turn, destroy a Civilian card</p>
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"We shot them, the people who heard too much of the Simurgh's song, who weren't just walking disaster areas, but who'd listened long enough that they lost something. Men, women and children missing that moral center that people like Miss Militia and I have"</text>
			<source>Director Tagg, Cell 22.2</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
</deck>