<?xml version="1.0"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="cards.xslt"?>

<deck>
	<deckname>PRT HQ</deckname>
	<version>1.0.0</version>
	<textcolour>black</textcolour>
	<cardcolour>white</cardcolour>
	<boxcolour>white</boxcolour>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<type>Drone</type><type>Device</type>
		<hp>5</hp>
		<text>At the end of the environment turn this card deals 1 energy damage to all non-environment targets with 2 or less HP</text>
		<name>Guard Drone</name>
		<quote>
			<text>They emulated Sere's power on a low enough level to kill bugs in the area without doing undue harm to any people, then became laser turrets, firing an invisible beam every second for about a minute, killing a bug with each shot.</text>
			<source>Cell 22.1</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<type>Drone</type><type>Device</type>
		<hp>6</hp>
		<text>Whenever a non-environment target deals 4 or more damage in one instance this card deals that target 4 lightning damage</text>
		<name>Prison Drone</name>
		<quote>
			<text>"Touch the door, make too much noise or use your power, and the room gets flooded with an electric charge"</text>
			<source>Triumph, Cell 22.1</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<type>Device</type>
		<hp>16</hp>
		<text>Whenever damage is dealt to all targets or all targets of a particular type reduce that damage by 1</text>
		<name>Base Forcefield</name>
		<quote>
			<text>Moments later, he heard the distinctive hiss-crack of forcefield generators failing (the base's?)</text>
			<source>Cenotaph, Cataclysm 7.1</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<hp>8</hp>
		<text><p>Whenever a player character card is dealt damage by this card that player discards a card.</p><p>At the end of the environment turn this card deals the non-environment target with the lowest HP 1 projectile damage</p></text>
		<name>Containment Agents</name>
		<quote>
			<text>Their very recognizable uniforms were chain mesh augmented with kevlar, topped with faceless helmets. The only means you had to identify them with were the badge numbers printed across their vests in bold white numbers.</text>
			<source>Tangle 6.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>5</hp>
		<text><p>At the end of the environment turn all Devices regain 2 HP.</p><p>At the end of the environment turn this card deals 1 energy damage to the non-environment target with the highest HP</p></text>
		<name>Kid Win</name>
		<quote>
			<text>The PRT staff insisted he was exceptional with antigrav and guns, had it even marked in his file, but he knew it wasn't so true. He finished his guns because they were simple, in their own way. It was easy enough to take three half-finished gun projects and mash them together.</text>
			<source>Sentinel 9.4</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>6</hp>
		<text>At the start of the environment turn select the player character card with the lowest HP. Until the next environment turn that character cannot draw cards, cannot deal damage, cannot use powers, cannot be damaged, and does not have a turn. If that player character card is the only player character card that is not incapacitated the heroes lose the game</text>
		<name>Clockblocker</name>
		<quote>
			<text>...they were just suspended in time. Stuck in the air, immobile, untouchable.</text>
			<source>Agitation 3.9</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>5</hp>
		<text><p>Reduce damage dealt to environment cards by 1.</p><p>Increase damage dealt by environment cards by 1</p></text>
		<name>Vista</name>
		<quote>
			<text>I stared at the world that stretched out before us, and it was wrong. Perspective was skewed. Lines bent where they should have been straight, and the expanse to our left was somehow more extensive than the space to our right.</text>
			<source>Venom 29.1</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>20</hp>
		<text>At the end of the environment turn this card deals 3 melee damage to the non-environment target with the second highest HP</text>
		<name>Aegis</name>
		<quote>
			<text>"Punctured lung, ma'am," Aegis rasped, "I think there's a hole in my front and back."  As if to demonstrate, he stuck his fingers into his chest cavity.</text>
			<source>Aegis, Interlude 3</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>5</hp>
		<text><p>Player character cards dealt damage by this card cannot use powers until the start of the environment turn.</p><p>At the end of the environment turn this card deals 2 projectile damage to the two non-environment targets with the most HP</p></text>
		<name>Gallant</name>
		<quote>
			<text>So he'd shot the dangerous psychopath with a blast that made her angry. Someone would have to explain that one to me at a later date.</text>
			<source>Agitation 3.10</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>6</hp>
		<text><p>Reduce damage dealt to this card by 1.</p><p>At the end of the environment turn this card deals 2 projectile damage to the non-environment target with the lowest HP</p></text>
		<name>Shadow Stalker</name>
		<quote>
			<text>"You're fun to irritate. And you know, it's cool. In the end, you're one of the people that's going to remember her. Someone that's left, who knows the general story. I don't think she's the schadenfreude type, but I think she'd appreciate that it's true, and that it nettles you just a little."</text>
			<source>Imp, Teneral e.2</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<type>Device</type>
		<text><p>At the start of the environment turn reveal cards from the top of the Environment deck until you reveal a Parahuman. Put the Parahuman into play and shuffle the other cards back into the environment deck.</p><p> At the start of a player turn that player may skip the rest of their turn to destroy this card</p></text>
		<name>Base Alarm</name>
		<quote>
			<text>Colin moved quickly, spinning in his chair to reach a small console. He opened a glass panel and flipped a switch. Air raid sirens immediately began their ominous whine.</text>
			<source>Interlude 7</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
</deck>