<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="cards.xslt"?>

<!-- LOGO: Lightning bolt -->

<villain
xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xmlns="http://www.jamespicone.name/parahumans"
xs:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../hero.xsd">
	<name>Behemoth</name>
	<version>2.0.0</version>
	<textcolour>black</textcolour>
	<cardcolour>white</cardcolour>
	<boxcolour>white</boxcolour>
	<villaincard>
		<name>Behemoth</name>
		<front>
			<title>Herokiller</title>
			<hp>100</hp>
			<nemesis>Alexandria</nemesis>
			<setup>Place Behemoth into play, "Herokiller" side up. Remove all Movement cards from the villain deck, shuffle them, and put them aside as the Movement Deck</setup>
			<gameplay>
				<p>Whenever Behemoth would deal damage, use Behemoth's current damage type.</p>
				<p>At the start of the villain turn, if Behemoth has less than 30 HP, flip Behemoth.</p>
				<p>At the start of the villain turn, play the top card of the Movement deck.</p>
				<p>At the end of the villain turn, Behemoth deals each hero X damage, where X is the number of proximity tokens on the hero.</p>
			</gameplay>
			<advanced>If a hero ever has 6 proximity tokens on them, they are immediately incapacitated</advanced>
		</front>
		<back>
			<title>Herokiller, Desperate</title>
			<hp>100</hp>
			<nemesis>Alexandria</nemesis>
			<gameplay>
				<p>Whenever Behemoth would deal damage, use Behemoth's current damage type.</p>
				<p>At the start of the villain turn, play the top card of the Movement deck.</p>
				<p>Whenever Behemoth would be dealt damage of his current damage type, redirect the damage to the hero target with the lowest HP.</p>
				<p>At the end of the villain turn, Behemoth deals each hero X damage, where X is the number of proximity tokens on the hero.</p>
				<p>At the end of the villain turn, play the top card of the villain deck</p>
			</gameplay>
			<advanced>If a hero ever has 6 proximity tokens on them, they are immediately incapacitated</advanced>
		</back>
	</villaincard>
	
	<!-- 10 movement cards -->
	
	<card>
		<name>Advance</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<type>Movement</type>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<text>Place a proximity token on every hero</text>
		
		<quote>
			<text>"Maintain a distance of at least a hundred feet from Behemoth at the very minimum."</text>
			<source>Chevalier, Drone 23.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Leap</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<type>Movement</type>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<text>Place 2 proximity tokens on a hero. Place 1 proximity token on the hero before and after that hero in the turn order</text>
		<quote>
			<text>With his claws and feet now on firm ground, he leaped. The shockwave of his departure toppled the slipshod buildings around him in his wake.</text>
			<source>Drone 23.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>A Shift of Attention</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<type>Movement</type>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<text>Remove every proximity token from a hero. Place them all on a different hero</text>
		<quote>
			<text>This was his new tactic, burrowing, surfacing. But where was the retaliation? Their whole damn pattern centered around repaying us twice over for any abuse we inflicted on them.</text>
			<source>Crushed 24.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>No Safety</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<type>Movement</type>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<text>Move 1 proximity token from every hero to the hero with the least proximity tokens</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"...Assume every structure will fall down in a heartbeat, and know that there's no good place to hide and wait for this to be over."</text>
			<source>Chevalier, Drone 23.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Shift</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<type>Movement</type>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<text>Move all proximity tokens on each hero to the hero to their right</text>
		
		<quote>
			<text>"...Get any closer, you probably won't have a chance of escaping if he decides to close the gap..."</text>
			<source>Chevalier, Drone 23.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Focus</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<type>Movement</type>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<text>Place a proximity token on a hero</text>
		
		<quote>
			<text>"...Be mindful of line of sight, because he can and will tag you with a lightning bolt, and it's not something you can dodge..."</text>
			<source>Chevalier, Drone 23.5</source>
		</quote>	
	</card>
	<!-- 5 one-shots -->
	
	<card>
		<name>Roar</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<text>
			<p>Behemoth's damage type is Sonic.</p>
			<p>Behemoth deals 2 damage to all non-villain targets.</p>
		</text>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>The creature roared, and as invulnerable as she was, it almost hurt.</text>
			<source>Interlude 15</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Lightning Bolt</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<text>
			<p>Behemoth's damage type is Lightning.</p>
			<p>Behemoth deals 5 damage to a hero. That hero may move a proximity token to another hero.</p>
		</text>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>A lightning bolt flashed from the tip of Behemoth's claw, arcing around her and striking one of her subordinates in a single heartbeat, before leaving only the smell of ozone.</text>
			<source>Interlude 15</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Discharge</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<text>
			<p>Behemoth's damage type is Energy.</p>
			<p>Behemoth deals 2 damage to each hero target. Each hero may move a proximity token to another hero</p>
		</text>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>"He's a dynakinetic! He manipulates energy! No Manton limitation!"</text>
			<source>Alexandria, Interlude 15</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Wildfire</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<text>
			<p>Behemoth's damage type is Fire.</p>
			<p>Behemoth deals H damage to any hero with 3 or more proximity tokens.</p>
			<p>Behemoth deals H damage to all non-character hero targets</p> 
		</text>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>When I looked back at the screen, nearly half of the city was on fire. Black smoke choked the skies, a stark contrast to the cloudy sky of only minutes ago.</text>
			<source>Drone 23.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<!-- 3 ongoing -->
	
	<card>
		<name>Unstoppable Advance</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<text>
			<p>When this card enters play, change Behemoth's damage type to Melee.</p>
			<p>At the end of the villain turn, move a proximity token to the hero with the most proximity tokens from any other hero</p>
		</text>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>Cryogenic beams, containment foam and more served to slow him down. Not stopping him. No, that was too much to hope for.</text>
			<source>Drone 23.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Juggernaut</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<text>
			<p>When this card enters play, change Behemoth's damage type to Sonic.</p>
			<p>Reduce damage dealt to Behemoth by 1</p>
			<p>Whenever a hero deals damage to Behemoth, move a proximity token to that hero from any other hero.</p>
		</text>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>Forty-five feet tall at the very least, he climbed forth from underground. His skin was crusted with black stone that might have been obsidian, layers of what might have been cooled magma sloughing off of him as he planted his feet on the ground and stood straight.</text>
			<source>Interlude 15</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Continuous Crackle</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<text>
			<p>When this card enters play, change Behemoth's damage type to Lightning.</p>
			<p>Whenever a hero puts an Equipment or Ongoing card into play, Behemoth deals that hero 2 damage.</p>
		</text>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>I took off. Again, I tried my armband. Static. Better than nothing, but not ideal.</text>
			<source>Crushed 24.4</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<!-- 5 Removal -->
	
	<card>
		<name>Twisted Wreckage</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<text>
			<p>Behemoth's damage type is Lightning.</p>
			<p>Destroy 2 hero non-character cards and remove one of them from the game. Move 1 proximity token to a hero who owned one of the destroyed cards from any other hero</p>
		</text>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>The Endbringer's path of destruction had continued more or less in one general direction, but beyond that, the damage was indiscriminate, indeterminate.</text>
			<source>Crushed 24.2</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Earthquake</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<text>
			<p>Behemoth's damage type is Melee</p>
			<p>Destroy all environment cards</p>
			<p>Destroy all ongoing cards</p>
			<p>Destroy all equipment cards</p>
			<p>Deal 2 damage to all hero targets</p>
		</text>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>As far as the eye could see in every direction, terrain shifted. Hillsides abruptly tilted, standing structures fell like collapsing houses of cards.</text>
			<source>Crushed 24.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Incinerate</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<text>
			<p>Behemoth's damage type is Fire.</p>
			<p>Destroy two ongoing cards. Move 1 proximity token from one of the heroes who owned one of the destroyed cards to another hero</p>
		</text>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>The man ignited from the inside out, flame and smoke pouring from every orifice as he was turned into a burned-out husk in a matter of seconds. His skeleton disintegrated into fine dust and ash as it crashed to the ground.</text>
			<source>Interlude 15</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
</villain>