<?xml version="1.0"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="cards.xslt"?>

<!-- LOGO: Snake -->

<deck>
	<deckname>Coil</deckname>
	<version>2.0</version>
	<villain>
		<name>Coil</name>
		<front>
			<setup>
				<p>Put Coil: Scheming and Coil: Acting into play, "Evil Mastermind" side up.</p>
				<p>Put Underground Base into play.</p>
				<p>Note that Coil: Scheming activates before Coil: Acting.</p>
			</setup>
		</front>
	</villain>
	
	<specialcard>
		<name>Coil: Scheming</name>
		<front>
			<title>Evil Mastermind</title>
			<nemesis>Tattletale</nemesis>
			<hp>50</hp>
			<text><p>At the start of the villain turn play the top card of the environment deck.</p><p>At the end of the villain turn all villain targets regain 2 HP.</p><p>When this card would be destroyed flip it instead</p></text>
			<advanced>At the end of the villain turn, if Coil: Acting has more HP than this card, set this card's HP to its HP</advanced>
		</front>
		<back>
			<title>Defeated</title>
			<text>If Coil: Acting is flipped to the "Defeated" side, the heroes win the game.</text>
			<advanced>At the end of the villain turn, flip this card and set its HP to Coil: Acting's HP</advanced>
		</back>
	</specialcard>
	<specialcard>
		<name>Coil: Acting</name>
		<front>
			<title>Evil Mastermind</title>
			<nemesis>Tattletale</nemesis>
			<hp>50</hp>
			<text><p>At the start of the villain turn reveal cards from the villain deck until you reveal a Parahuman. Put it into play then shuffle the other revealed cards into the villain deck.</p><p>At the end of the villain turn deal H energy damage to the hero target with the highest HP.</p><p>When this card would be destroyed, flip it instead</p></text>
			<advanced>At the end of the villain turn if Coil: Scheming has more HP than this card set this card's HP to its HP</advanced>
		</front>
		<back>
			<title>Defeated</title>
			<text>If Coil: Scheming is flipped to the "Defeated" side, the heroes win the game.</text>
			<advanced>At the end of the villain turn, flip this card and set its HP to Coil: Scheming's HP.</advanced>
		</back>
	</specialcard>
	<card>
		<name>Underground Base</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<text>Villain targets are immune to damage from Environment cards</text>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>The interior of the sub-basement had none of the smell of the previous chambers, and consisted of two tiers with walls of poured concrete. The upper level we stood on was an arrangement of metal walkways that extended around the room’s perimeter. Crates and boxes filled the level below, and I could see fifteen or so of Coil’s people down there, sitting on crates or leaning against them, talking among themselves.</text>
			<source>Buzz 7.11</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Mercenaries</name>
		<hp>6</hp>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<text>At the end of the villain turn, this card deals H - 1 energy damage to the two hero targets with the highest HP</text>
		<quote>
			<text>Each soldier was outfitted in a matching uniform: shades of gray and some black, hard vests with raised collars to protect their necks. Only a few wore their balaclavas, and I could see a variety of nationalities in a group that was mostly men. All of the soldiers had assault rifles somewhere nearby, slung over shoulders with straps and leaning against walls or crates.</text>
			<source>Buzz 7.11</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Sundancer</name>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>10</hp>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<text><p>This card is immune to fire damage.</p><p>At the end of the villain turn, this card deals 2 fire damage to all hero targets</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>Directly below Sundancer, the floor was normal. Starting around five feet from her, though, the ground looked wet, glassy.

The asphalt was melting.</text>
			<source>Hive 5.9</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Trickster</name>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>6</hp>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<text><p>The first time Trickster would be dealt damage each round, redirect it to the hero target with the lowest HP.</p><p>At the end of the villain turn, the hero with most cards in play destroys one of their cards</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>"A shame," Trickster bowed.

In the blink of an eye, Weld disappeared, and Genesis loomed in his place</text>
			<source>Sentinel 9.3</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Genesis</name>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>8</hp>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<text><p>When this card is destroyed, shuffle it back into the villain deck.</p><p>At the end of the villain turn, this card deals 2 poison damage to H hero targets</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>Genesis had decided on a form that was an overlarge woman’s face carved out of bone, surrounded by long, thin, branching tentacles.</text>
			<source>Colony 15.10</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Ballistic</name>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>10</hp>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<text><p>Whenever a hero card is dealt damage by this card, that hero must destroy one of their cards.</p><p>At the end of the villain turn, this card deals H + 1 projectile damage to the hero target with the highest HP</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>When he used his power on the car, you didn’t see it move. Rather, in the blink of an eye, it was gone from where it had been, abruptly in a position where it was virtually wrapped around the upper half of the forcefield.</text>
			<source>Tangle 6.7</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Dinah</name>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>5</hp>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<text><p>Coil: Scheming and Coil: Acting are immune to damage.</p><p>Whenever this card is dealt damage during a hero's turn, that hero must discard a card</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>"The last thing I want is another arrogant dickface telling me what to do," Dinah said. "You want answers, Director? Fine. Twenty two point eight one three percent chance you die painfully, over long, slow minutes or hours. Maybe soon, maybe in twenty years, but it’ll bring you to tears, and you’ll wail in pain. That’s a freebie. Want more details?"</text>
			<source>Dinah, Cell 22.1</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Circus</name>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>4</hp>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<text><p>Whenever a hero card is played, this card deals that hero 1 projectile damage</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>Dauntless parried Circus’ sledgehammer with his Arclance, and the sledgehammer was gone in the next second, as though it had never existed. At some point in the meantime, though, she’d managed to slip a lit torch into one hand.</text>
			<source>Tangle 6.7</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Trainwreck</name>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>12</hp>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<text><p>Whenever a non-villain target would damage a villain target other than Trainwreck, redirect the damage to Trainwreck.</p><p>At the start of the villain turn, Trainwreck regains H HP</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>A steel giant with massive hands and a spout on its back that was spewing volumes of gray-black smoke had one hand closed around Armsmaster. Repeatedly, methodically, it slammed Armsmaster against the hood of a car.</text>
			<source>Tangle 6.7</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>I Know All Your Tricks</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<text>Destroy all hero Ongoing cards</text>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>"He’s found a way to confuse my power, to counteract it. This thing with the hit on your head. It was just to scare us. To let us know that any security my power afforded us, it doesn’t apply to him."</text>
			<source>Tattletale, Colony 15.10</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Trickery and Deceit</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<text>Destroy all hero Equipment cards</text>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>Über kicking down the door, leaving the heroes to deal with the bomb they were holding, which was squealing at a higher pitch and volume with every passing second. It was glowing, brilliant in its golden radiance.</text>
			<source>Monarch 16.8</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Let's Try Something Else</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<text><p>Put the villain trash on top of the villain deck.</p><p>Shuffle the villain deck.</p><p>Play the top card of the villain deck</p></text>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>"Do not use grenades. I assure you it does not work out the way you imagine it will. Give me that."</text>
			<source>Coil, Monarch 16.11</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>A Backup For Every Asset</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<text>Take all Ongoing cards out of the villain trash and put them into play</text>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>"Maybe," she admitted, "But that still feels wrong. Why wouldn’t Coil have a backup plan?"</text>
			<source>Tattletale, Colony 15.10</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Teleporter</name>
		<hp>8</hp>
		<type>Device</type>
		<text>At the start of the villain turn, reveal cards from the top of the villain deck until you have revealed H targets. Put the revealed targets into play and shuffle the rest of the revealed cards back into the villain deck</text>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>He snapped his fingers, and soldiers began to teleport down to the edges of the market.</text>
			<source>Monarch 16.13</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Two Bites at Every Cherry</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<text><p>Increase damage dealt by villain targets by 1.</p><p>Damage dealt by villain cards is irreducible</p></text>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>"Tattletale clued me in. He creates parallel realities. Makes two different decisions, and he gets to see the outcome of each as they unfold. Decides which he wants in the end."</text>
			<source>Skitter, Colony 15.4</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Plans Within Plans</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<text>Reduce damage dealt to villain targets by 2</text>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>Screws. Screws with <em>hexagonal slots</em>. Because Calvert wasn’t willing to risk that I’d have a screwdriver on hand with a more typical head on it.</text>
			<source>Monarch 16.11</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
</deck>