<?xml version="1.0"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="cards.xslt"?>

<!-- LOGO: Do the travellers have a logo? A hydra? -->

<deck>
	<deckname>Echidna</deckname>
	<version>2.0.0</version>
	<textcolour>black</textcolour>
	<cardcolour>white</cardcolour>
	<boxcolour>white</boxcolour>
	<villain>
		<name>Echidna</name>
		<front>
			<title>Mother of Monsters</title>
			<hp>40</hp>
			<nemesis>Skitter</nemesis>
			<setup>
				<p>At the start of the game Echidna enters play Mother of Monsters side up.</p>
				<p>Take out and shuffle all Twisted cards; put them aside as the Twisted side-deck.</p>
				<p>Put the top H - 2 cards of the Twisted side-deck into play</p>
			</setup>
			<gameplay>
				<p>Whenever a hero card enters the trash, Echidna regains 1 HP</p>
				<p>At the end of the villain turn, Echidna deals H - 1 melee damage to the 2 hero targets with the lowest HP.</p>
				<p>At the end of the villain turn, if no hero was dealt damage by a villain card last round, flip Echidna</p>
			</gameplay>
			<advanced>Reduce damage dealt to Echidna by 1</advanced>
		</front>
		<back>
			<title>Noelle, Canny Tactician</title>
			<hp>40</hp>
			<nemesis>Skitter</nemesis>
			<gameplay>
				<p>When flipped to this side, destroy H hero cards</p>
				<p>Whenever a hero card enters the trash, Echidna regains 1 HP</p>
				<p>At the start of the villain turn, search the villain deck for an 'Engulfed' card, put it into play, and shuffle the villain deck. Then flip Echidna</p>
			</gameplay>
			<advanced>When flipped to this side, search the villain deck for an 'Engulfed' card and put it into play. Shuffle the villain deck</advanced>
		</back>
	</villain>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Parahuman</class>
		<class>Twisted</class>
		<name>Alexandria</name>
		<hp>14</hp>
		<text><p>At the end of the villain turn, Alexandria deals 2 melee damage to the hero with the highest HP</p>
		<p>The hero with the highest HP cannot use powers</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>An Alexandria.  Had to be, with that long black hair.  The woman stood, and I could see how she was missing an eye.  She brushed her hair to one side, so it covered half her face, and I could hear a murmur.</text>
			<source>Scourge 19.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Parahuman</class>
		<class>Twisted</class>
		<name>Armsmaster</name>
		<hp>10</hp>
		<text><p>At the end of the villain turn, destroy a hero Equipment card</p>
		<p>Whenever an equipment card is put into play, Armsmaster regains 5 HP</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>“She’s ambushing him.  There’s a Leet with a gun inside the building behind him.  Tinker made, has to be.”</text>
			<source>Skitter, Queen 18.7</source>
		</quote>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Parahuman</class>
		<class>Twisted</class>
		<name>Assault</name>
		<hp>10</hp>
		<text><p>At the start of each hero turn, Assault deals that hero 1 melee damage</p>
		<p>Assault is immune to melee damage</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text></text>
			<source></source>
		</quote>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Parahuman</class>
		<class>Twisted</class>
		<name>Battery</name>
		<hp>10</hp>
		<text><p>At the start of the villain turn, play the top card of the villain deck</p>
		<p>At the end of the villain turn, Battery deals 2 melee damage to the hero target with the lowest HP</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text></text>
			<source></source>
		</quote>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Parahuman</class>
		<class>Twisted</class>
		<name>Dauntless</name>
		<hp>12</hp>
		<text><p>At the end of the villain turn, place a charge token on Dauntless</p>
		<p>At the start of the villain turn, Dauntless deals the hero target with the highest HP X energy damage, where X = the number of charge tokens on Dauntless + 2</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text></text>
			<source></source>
		</quote>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Parahuman</class>
		<class>Twisted</class>
		<name>Eidolon</name>
		<hp>8</hp>
		<text>
			<p>This card can't be put into play during setup. If it would be, shuffle it back into the Twisted deck and put another one into play.</p>
			<p>At the end of the villain turn, Eidolon deals 5 psychic damage to all hero targets</p>
			<p>At the start of the villain turn, if there's a Power token on Eidolon, lose the game. Otherwise, put a Power token on Eidolon</p>
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>We charged.  There was no other choice.  If we didn’t win now, everyone lost.</text>
			<source>Scourge 19.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Parahuman</class>
		<class>Twisted</class>
		<name>Grue</name>
		<hp>12</hp>
		<text><p>At the end of the villain turn, put the top card of the Twisted deck into play, then shuffle the Twisted with the lowest HP back into the Twisted deck</p>
		<p>Reduce damage dealt to villain targets by 1</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text></text>
			<source></source>
		</quote>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Parahuman</class>
		<class>Twisted</class>
		<name>Glory Girl</name>
		<hp>8</hp>
		<text><p>At the end of the villain turn, Glory Girl deals 1 psychic damage to all hero targets</p>
		<p>Prevent the first damage dealt to Glory Girl each round</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text></text>
			<source></source>
		</quote>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Parahuman</class>
		<class>Twisted</class>
		<name>Panacea</name>
		<hp>6</hp>
		<text><p>At the end of the villain turn, all villain targets regain 2 HP</p>
		<p>The first time each round a villain target other than Panacea would be reduced to 0 or less HP, set its HP to 1 instead</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text></text>
			<source></source>
		</quote>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Parahuman</class>
		<class>Twisted</class>
		<name>Labyrinth</name>
		<hp>10</hp>
		<text><p>Villain cards cannot be damaged or destroyed by environment cards</p>
		<p>Put the top card of the Environment deck into play</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text></text>
			<source></source>
		</quote>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Parahuman</class>
		<class>Twisted</class>
		<name>Legend</name>
		<hp>12</hp>
		<text><p>At the end of the villain turn, Legend deals the hero target with the highest HP 2 irreducible energy damage</p>
		<p>Whenever Legend takes damage, increase the next damage he deals by 1</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text></text>
			<source></source>
		</quote>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Parahuman</class>
		<class>Twisted</class>
		<name>Miss Militia</name>
		<hp>10</hp>
		<text><p>At the end of the villain turn, Miss Militia deals 2 projectile damage to all hero targets</p>
		<p>When a hero plays a card, Miss Militia deals that hero 1 projectile damage</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text></text>
			<source></source>
		</quote>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Parahuman</class>
		<class>Twisted</class>
		<name>Regent</name>
		<hp>10</hp>
		<text><p>At the end of the villain turn, the hero target with the least HP deals itself 2 psychic damage</p>
		<p>Whenever Regent is dealt damage, Regent deals the target damaging him 1 psychic damage</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text></text>
			<source></source>
		</quote>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Parahuman</class>
		<class>Twisted</class>
		<name>Skitter</name>
		<hp>10</hp>
		<text><p>At the end of each villain turn, Skitter deals all hero targets 1 toxic damage</p>
		<p>Increase damage dealt by villain targets by 1</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text></text>
			<source></source>
		</quote>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Parahuman</class>
		<class>Twisted</class>
		<name>Tattletale</name>
		<hp>10</hp>
		<text><p>At the start of the villain turn, reveal the top two cards of the villain deck. If they don't share a type, put them both into play, in the order they were on the deck</p>
		<p>Villain targets are immune to psychic damage</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text></text>
			<source></source>
		</quote>
	</card>

	<!--
		Bunch of 'twisted' special cards here, ideally one per hero in the game at least, maybe even one per major parahuman. These are all targets with 'Twisted' and 'Parahuman' as types, they do annoying things and have frustratingly high HP.
	-->
	<card>
		<name>Engulfed</name>
		<type>Ongoing</type>
		<quantity>5</quantity>
		<text>
			<p>Place this card next to a hero that does not already have an 'Engulfed' card next to them. If you do, play the top card of the Twisted side-deck.</p>
			<p>The hero this card is next to must skip a phase (play, power, draw) each turn.</p>
			<p>Whenever the hero this card is next to skips a phase, they deal themselves 2 psychic damage</p>
			<p>If this card is not next to a hero target, destroy it</p>
			</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"The capes she keeps spitting out. Circus, Über, Leet and Vista. She's holding the four of them inside her, so she can keep creating more clones."</text>
			<source>Skitter, Queen 18.7</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Chimaerical Nightmare</name>
		<type>Ongoing</type>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<text>Reduce damage dealt to Echidna by 2. A the end of the villain turn, Echidna regains 2 HP</text>
		<quote>
			<text>The head of an animal, half-bovine and half-canine, extended from the front, large as a horse from the back of its skull to the tip of its flaring nostrils. Another head was in progress, emerging just to the left. Two forelegs extended to either side of the heads, rippling with powerful muscle, ending in something that fell between claw and hoof, massive and easily capable of tearing through steel.</text>
			<source>Migration 17.8</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Experimentation</name>
		<type>One-Shot</type>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<text>Reveal the top X cards of the villain deck, where X is the number of Twisted cards in play + 1. Put any revealed One-Shot cards or Engulfed cards into play. Shuffle the remaining cards back into the deck</text>
		<quote>
			<text>If one in a hundred capes met that kind of standard where they were just that much more versatile or powerful, then Echidna could make a hundred capes, and chances were good that one of those would be exceptional in that way.</text>
			<source>Scourge 19.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<type>One-Shot</type>
		<name>Bullrush</name>
		<text>
			<p>Echidna deals H+2 melee damage to the hero target with the lowest HP</p>
			<p>search the villain deck for an 'Engulfed' card and put it into play. Shuffle the villain deck</p>
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>That said, she charged. The ground shook with her advance, and the heroes only stood and watched, no doubt considering the possibility that I was right, that they could negotiate their way out of all this.</text>
			<source>Scourge 19.6</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<type>Ongoing</type>
		<name>Squad Tactics</name>
		<text>Increase damage dealt by villain targets by 1</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"She was the leader before all of this started, yeah. You have to understand, she's a natural tactician, and tacticians come in two varieties. There's the strategists that think things through, innovate, and analyze. Then there's ones that go by instinct. Noelle's the latter. Not to say she isn't good if given a chance to plan, but she can get a sense of the current dynamic on an intuitive level, play things by ear while making spur of the moment calls. Those calls turn out to be the right ones, not because she's lucky, but because she grasps the situation so quickly that it looks like she didn't give it any thought at all."</text>
			<source>Ballistic, Queen 18.2</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<type>One-Shot</type>
		<name>Crush</name>
		<text>Echidna deals H damage to any hero target with an 'Engulfed' card next to them</text>
		<quote>
			<text>Noelle tagged several of the bodies in her internal stomachs, felt flesh constrict tight against them</text>
			<source>Interlude 18</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<type>Ongoing</type>
		<name>Psychological Warfare</name>
		<text>At the start of the villain turn Echidna deals 2 psychic damage to all hero targets</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"...I'll hunt you down, I'll copy you until you're all used up, let your copies ruin your reputations and your lives, and then I'll eat you. I'll do it to each of you, one by one, until you realize it's easier to go after the Undersiders than to come after me. Give me my revenge, and this ends."</text>
			<source>Echidna, Queen 18.4</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<type>Ongoing</type>
		<name>Clone Army</name>
		<text>At the end of the villain turn, play the top card of the Twisted side-deck</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"...If she absorbs something alive, she clones it. More clones if she's angrier, we think. We don't have a large sample size of incidents."</text>
			<source>Ballistic, Queen 18.2</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<name>Slippery</name>
		<type>One-Shot</type>
		<text>A hero may discard their hand. If they don't, Echidna is immune to damage until the start of her next turn</text>
		<quote>
			<text>But the Kudzu's death wasn't instantaneous, and she had time for one last gesture. Echidna vibrated, and then split off into four copies.</text>
			<source>Scourge 19.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
</deck>