<?xml version="1.0"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="cards.xslt"?>

<!-- LOGO: Do the travellers have a logo? A hydra? -->

<deck>
	<deckname>Echidna</deckname>
	<version>1.0</version>
	<villain>
		<name>Echidna</name>
		<front>
			<title>Mother of Monsters</title>
			<hp>30</hp>
			<nemesis>Skitter</nemesis>
			<setup>At the start of the game Echidna enters play Mother of Monsters side up. Search the villain deck for all Twisted cards; shuffle them, and put the top H + 2 to the side as the Twisted side-deck. Set the other Twisted cards aside</setup>
			<gameplay>
				<p>When flipped to this side, Echidna deals H + 2 melee damage to the hero target with the highest HP</p>
				<p>Whenever a card enters the trash, Echidna regains 1 HP</p>
			<p>Whenever Echidna deals at least 8 - H damage in a single instance, search the villain deck and trash for an 'Engulfed' card, and put it into play</p>
			<p>At the end of the villain turn, if no hero target took damage in the last round, flip Echidna</p></gameplay>
			<advanced>Reduce damage dealt to Echidna by 1</advanced>
		</front>
		<back>
			<title>Noelle, Canny Tactician</title>
			<hp>30</hp>
			<nemesis>Skitter</nemesis>
			<gameplay><p>When flipped to this side, destroy H hero cards</p>
				<p>Whenever a card enters the trash, Echidna regains 1 HP</p>
				<p>At the start of the villain turn, flip Echidna</p>
			</gameplay>
			<advanced>When flipped to this side, search the villain deck and trash for an 'Engulfed' card and put it into play</advanced>
		</back>
	</villain>
	<card>
		<name>Engulfed</name>
		<type>Ongoing</type>
		<quantity>5</quantity>
		<text>
			<p>Place this card next to a hero that does not already have an 'Engulfed' card next to them.</p>
			<p>The hero this card is next to must skip a phase (play, power, draw) each turn.</p>
			<p>Whenever the hero this card is next to skips a phase, they deal themselves 2 psychic damage</p> 
			<p>Play the top card of the Twisted side-deck</p>
			<p>If this card is not next to a hero target, destroy it</p>
			</text>
		<quote>
			<text></text>
			<source></source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Chimaerical Nightmare</name>
		<type>Ongoing</type>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<text>Reduce damage dealt to Echidna by 2. A the end of the villain turn, Echidna regains 2 HP</text>
		<quote>
			<text></text>
			<source></source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Experimentation</name>
		<type>One-Shot</type>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<text>Reveal the top X cards of the villain deck, where X is the number of Twisted cards in play + 1. Put any revealed One-Shots into play. Shuffle the remaining cards back into the deck</text>
		<quote>
			<text></text>
			<source></source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<type>One-Shot</type>
		<name>Bullrush</name>
		<text>Echidna deals H melee damage to the hero target with the lowest HP</text>
		<quote>
			<text></text>
			<source></source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<type>Ongoing</type>
		<name>Squad Tactics</name>
		<text>Increase damage dealt by villain targets by 1</text>
		<quote>
			<text></text>
			<source></source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<type>One-Shot</type>
		<name>Crush</name>
		<text>Echidna deals H damage to any hero target with an 'Engulfed' card next to them</text>
		<quote>
			<text></text>
			<source></source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<type>Ongoing</type>
		<name>Psychological Warfare</name>
		<text>At the start of the villain turn Echidna deals 2 psychic damage to all hero targets</text>
		<quote>
			<text></text>
			<source></source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<name>Slippery</name>
		<type>One-Shot</type>
		<text>A hero may discard their hand. If they don't, Echidna is immune to damage until the start of her next turn</text>
		<quote>
			<text></text>
			<source></source>
		</quote>
	</card>
</deck>