<?xml version="1.0"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="cards.xslt"?>

<!-- LOGO: Tidal wave -->

<deck>
	<deckname>Leviathan</deckname>
	<version>1.2</version>
	<textcolour>black</textcolour>
	<cardcolour>white</cardcolour>
	<boxcolour>white</boxcolour>
	<villain>
		<name>Leviathan</name>
		<front>
			<title>Citykiller</title>
			<hp>100</hp>
			<nemesis>Dauntless</nemesis>
			<setup>Put Leviathan into play "Citykiller" side up. Reveal cards from the top of the villain deck until you reveal a Tactic card; put it into play. Shuffle the other cards back into the villain deck</setup>
			<gameplay><p>When flipped to this side, destroy H hero cards</p><p>At the end of the villain turn, Leviathan deals 2 melee damage to all hero targets.</p><p>At the end of the villain turn, if Leviathan has been dealt 8 - H damage in one instance last round, flip Leviathan</p></gameplay>
			<advanced>Reduce damage dealt to Leviathan by 1</advanced>
		</front>
		<back>
			<title>Citykiller Retaliates</title>
			<hp>100</hp>
			<nemesis>Dauntless</nemesis>
			<gameplay><p>When flipped to this side, reveal cards from the top of the villain deck until you reveal a Tactic card. Put it into play; shuffle the rest of the revealed cards back into the villain deck.</p>
			<p>At the start of the villain turn, flip Leviathan</p>
			<p>Reduce damage dealt to Leviathan by 1</p></gameplay>
			<advanced>The first time Leviathan would flip each turn, play the top card of the villain deck first</advanced>
		</back>
	</villain>
	
	<card>
		<name>Water Shadow</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Tactic</type>
		<text>Whenever Leviathan would deal melee damage to a target, this card deals that target 2 irreducible melee damage. This card is indestructible</text>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Torrential Downpour</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Tactic</type>
		<text>Whenever a player would draw a card, Leviathan deals that player's character card 1 cold damage. This card is indestructible</text>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Lose the War</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Tactic</type>
		<text><p>If the environment deck is ever empty, the heroes lose the game. At the end of the villain turn, remove the top card of the environment deck from the game.</p>
		<p>Players may skip any of their phases (play, power, draw). Any time a player skips a phase, they may take a card from the environment trash and shuffle it back into the environment deck</p>
		<p>This card is indestructible</p></text>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Faster Than You'd Think</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Tactic</type>
		<text>The first time Leviathan would be dealt damage each round, prevent that damage. This card is indestructible</text>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Impossible Strength</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<text>Increase damage dealt by villain cards by 1</text>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Impossible Toughness</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<text>Reduce damage dealt to Leviathan by 1</text>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Impossible Endurance</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<text>At the start of the villain turn, reveal cards from the top of the villain trash until you reveal a one-shot. Play it, and then shuffle the other revealed cards back into the villain trash</text>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Tidal Wave</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<text>Destroy all environment targets. Leviathan deals X cold damage to all non-villain targets, where X = 1 + the number of cards destroyed in this way</text>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Cunning</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<text>Play the top 2 cards of the villain deck</text>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Anyone Can Die</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<text>Leviathan deals the hero target with the highest HP 5 irreducible melee damage</text>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Guile</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<text>Flip Leviathan</text>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Whipping Tail</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<text>Leviathan deals 2 melee damage to the 2 hero targets with the lowest HP</text>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
	</card>
</deck>