<?xml version="1.0"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="villain_convert.xslt"?>

<deck>
	<name>Leviathan</name>
	<version>1.0</version>
	<villain>
		<name>Leviathan</name>
		<front>
			<title>Citykiller</title>
			<hp>100</hp>
			<nemesis>Dauntless</nemesis>
			<setup>Put Leviathan into play "Citykiller" side up. Search Leviathan's deck for Water Shadow and put it into play</setup>
			<gameplay>When flipped to this side, destroy H hero cards<br/><br/>At the end of the villain turn, Leviathan deals 2 melee damage to all hero targets.<br/>At the end of the villain turn, if Leviathan has been dealt H damage in one instance last round, flip Leviathan</gameplay>
			<advanced>Reduce damage dealt to Leviathan by 1</advanced>
		</front>
		<back>
			<title>Citykiller Retaliates</title>
			<hp>100</hp>
			<nemesis>Dauntless</nemesis>
			<gameplay>At the start of the villain turn, flip Leviathan<br/><br/>Reduce damage dealt to Leviathan by 1
			<advanced>Whenever Leviathan would flip, play the top card of the villain deck</advanced>
		</back>
	</villain>
	
	<card>
		<name>Water Shadow</name>
		<type>Ongoing</type>
		<text>Whenever Leviathan would deal damage to a target, this card deals that target 2 irreducible melee damage. This card is indestructible</text>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Torrential Downpour</name>
		<type>Ongoing</type>
		<text>At the start of each hero turn, Leviathan deals that hero 1 cold damage</text>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Lose the War</name>
		<type>Ongoing</type>
		<text>If the environment deck is ever empty, the heroes lose the game. At the end of the villain turn, remove the top card of the environment deck from the game</text>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Faster Than You'd Think</name>
		<type>Ongoing</type>
		<text>The first time Leviathan would be dealt damage each round, prevent that damage</text>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Impossible Strength</name>
		<type>Ongoing</type>
		<text>Increase damage dealt by villain cards by 1</text>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Impossible Toughness</name>
		<type>Ongoing</type>
		<text>Reduce damage dealt to Leviathan by 1</text>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Tidal Wave</name>
		<type>One-Shot</type>
		<text>Destroy all environment targets. Leviathan deals X cold damage to all non-villain targets, where X = 1 + the number of cards destroyed in this way</text>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Cunning</name>
		<type>One-Shot</type>
		<text>Play the top 2 cards of the villain deck</text>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Anyone Can Die</name>
		<type>One-Shot</type>
		<text>Leviathan deals the hero target with the highest HP 5 irreducible melee damage</text>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Guile</name>
		<type>One-Shot</type>
		<text>Flip Leviathan. Play the top card of the villain deck</text>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Whipping Tail</name>
		<type>One-Shot</type>
		<text>Leviathan deals 1 melee damage to the 2 hero targets with the lowest HP</text>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
	</card>
</deck>