<?xml version="1.0"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="villain_convert.xslt"?>

<deck>
	<name>Lung</name>
	<version>1.1</version>
	<villain>
		<name>Lung</name>
		<front>
			<title>Gang Leader</title>
			<hp>90</hp>
			<nemesis>Skitter</nemesis>
			<setup>At the start of the game Lung enters play Gang Leader side up. Put Brute into play, Gang Leader side up.</setup>
			<gameplay>When the villain trash is shuffled into the villain deck, flip Brute, and flip Lung.</gameplay>
			<advanced>At the end of the villain turn, discard the top 3 cards of the villain deck</advanced>
		</front>
		<back>
			<title>Dragon Awoken</title>
			<hp>90</hp>
			<nemesis>Skitter</nemesis>
			<gameplay><p>When flipped to this side, destroy all villain cards in play and put all cards in the villain deck into the villain trash.</p>				
				<p>Villain cards cannot be played.</p>
				<p>Reduce damage dealt to Lung by 2.</p>
			</gameplay>
			<advanced>When flipped to this side, the heroes lose the game</advanced>
		</back>
	</villain>
	<specialcard>
		<name>Brute</name>
		<front>
		<title>Gang Leader</title>
		<text><p>This card is indestructible.</p>
		<p>If there are 10 or more cards in the villain trash, reduce damage dealt to Lung by 1.</p>
		<p>At the end of the villain turn play the top card of the villain deck, then:
			<ul>
				<li>Lung deals X melee damage to all hero targets, where X = 1 + the number of cards in the villain trash / 5 then,</li>
				<li>If there are 5 or more cards in the villain trash, Lung regains 1 HP then,</li>
				<li>If there are 15 or more cards in the villain trash, Lung regains 1 HP.</li>
			</ul>
		</p>
		</text>
		</front>
		<back>
		<title>Dragon Awoken</title>
		<text>
		<p>This card is indestructible</p>
		<p>Lung is immune to damage dealt by Environment cards.</p>
		<p>
			At the end of the villain turn:
				<ul>
					<li>Lung deals 6 melee and 2 irreducible fire damage to all hero targets then,</li>
					<li>Lung regains 3 HP then,</li>
					<li>Destroy H hero ongoing or equipment cards.</li>
				</ul>
				</p>
		</text>
		</back>
	</specialcard>
	<card>
		<name>Burst of Flame</name>
		<type>One-Shot</type>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<text>Lung deals the hero target with the highest HP X fire damage, where X = 1 + the number of cards in the villain trash / 2</text>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Smash</name>
		<type>One-Shot</type>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<text>Lung deals the hero target with the lowest HP 2 melee damage. Destroy 1 hero ongoing or equipment card</text>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Growing Anger</name>
		<type>One-Shot</type>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<text>Discard the top 3 cards of the villain deck. Play the top card of the villain deck</text>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<type>Ongoing</type>
		<name>Wings</name>
		<text>Lung is immune to damage from Environment cards</text>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<type>Ongoing</type>
		<name>White-Hot Flame</name>
		<text>Fire damage dealt by Lung is irreducible</text>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<type>Ongoing</type>
		<name>Pyrokinesis</name>
		<text>Whenever Lung deals melee damage to a target, Lung deals 2 fire damage to that target</text>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<type>Ongoing</type>
		<name>Terrible Burns</name>
		<text>Whenever a hero is dealt fire damage by Lung, destroy 1 hero ongoing or equipment card. At the end of the villain turn, Lung deals the hero target with the highest HP H - 2 fire damage</text>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<name>Bakuda</name>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>6</hp>
		<text>At the start of the villain turn, reveal the top card of the villain deck. If it is a one-shot, Bakuda deals 5 fire damage to all non-villain targets. If it is an ongoing, each hero discards 1 card. If it is a target, the hero with the most cards in play destroys all of them</text>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<name>Oni Lee</name>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>3</hp>
		<text>At the end of the villain turn, Oni Lee deals the hero target with the lowest HP 3 melee damage. Whenever Oni Lee would take damage, reveal the top card of the villain deck. If it is a one-shot prevent the damage. Shuffle the revealed card back into the villain deck</text>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<name>ABB Thugs</name>
		<type>Thug</type>
		<hp>4</hp>
		<text>At the end of the villain turn, ABB Thugs deal the hero target with the lowest HP 2 projectile damage</text>
	</card>	
</deck>