<?xml version="1.0"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="cards.xslt"?>

<!-- LOGO: Capital M with vertical lines through it (like $) -->

<deck>
	<deckname>The Merchants</deckname>
	<version>1.0.0</version>
	<textcolour>black</textcolour>
	<cardcolour>white</cardcolour>
	<boxcolour>white</boxcolour>
	<villain>
		<name>Skidmark</name>
		<front>
			<title>Superpowered Drug Lord</title>
			<nemesis>Miss Militia</nemesis>
			<hp>45</hp>
			<setup>Place Skidmark in play, "Superpowered Drug Dealer" side up. Search the villain deck for all Thug cards; put them aside as the 'Thug deck'.</setup>
			<gameplay>
				<p>If the Thug deck is empty at the start of the villain turn, the heroes lose the game.</p>
				<p>At the end of the villain turn, play H - 1 Thugs from the top of the Thug deck.</p>
				<p>When this target is destroyed, flip it instead</p>
			</gameplay>
			<advanced>Reduce damage dealt to villain targets by 1.</advanced>
		</front>
		<back>
			<title>Defeated Drug Lord</title>
			<gameplay>
				<p>If the Thug deck is empty at the start of the villain turn, the heroes lose the game.</p>
				<p>At the end of the villain turn, play 1 Thug from the top of the Thug deck.</p>
				<p>If there are no villain targets in play, the heroes win the game</p>
			</gameplay>
		</back>
	</villain>
	<card>
		<name>Festival of Blood</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<text>Increase damage dealt by villain targets by 1</text>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>"You piss-licking losers know what the red armband means! Bloodshed! Violence! We've got ourselves a free for all brawl!"</text>
			<source>Skidmark, Infestation 11.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Festival of Excess</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<text>Reduce damage dealt to villain targets by 1</text>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>"Green armband means poison, and this is a poison half of you wastes of air have already tasted! We're gonna make it as bad as it gets! The worst of bad trips!"</text>
			<source>Skidmark, Interlude 12</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Festival of Love</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<text>At the start of the villain turn, play the top card of the Thug deck</text>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>They smiled as they posed provocatively and hugged the mannequins, showing off the clothes.</text>
			<source>Infestation 11.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Not Exactly Sanitary</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<text>Whenever a villain target deals non-toxic damage to another target, the villain target deals 1 toxic damage to that target</text>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>One man helped by a kid who might have been his son upended a trash can on the glowing ground to send rotted food and other rubbish flying into the ring.</text>
			<source>Infestation 11.6</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Squealer</name>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>8</hp>
		<text><p>Ignore villain targets when determining targeting for damage from Environment cards.</p><p>At the start of the villain turn, play the top card in the environment deck</p></text>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>Squealer had apparently never grasped the concept of elegance in design. From what I'd read and heard, she went for size, augmentations and additions when she built her vehicles. She was kind of the polar opposite of Armsmaster in that regard.</text>
			<source>Plague 12.2</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Mush</name>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>10</hp>
		<text><p>This card is immune to melee and projectile damage.</p><p>At the end of the villain turn, Mush deals 1 melee damage to all hero targets</p></text>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>His other arm and much of his lower body had already gathered some garbage around it, letting him stand several feet taller than he had before. The skin of his head and body was peeling off into more tendrils, reaching for more trash and distributing some from his arms to his torso.</text>
			<source>Infestation 11.7</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Scrub</name>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>10</hp>
		<text>At the start of the villain turn, Scrub deals 5 energy damage to all targets (except himself) with a HP evenly divisible by 3</text>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>Another flash sparked in the ring, then a second. Both were in close proximity to a boy no older than I was. White smoke poured from his eyes, nose, ears and mouth, with smaller traces flowing from his scalp, stirring his hair.</text>
			<source>Infestation 11.6</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Helicopter</name>
		<type>Device</type>
		<hp>16</hp>
		<text><p>Skidmark is immune to melee damage.</p><p>At the end of the villain turn, play the top card of the Thug deck</p></text>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>Squealer's vehicle was like a helicopter made by someone who had never seen a helicopter before, who'd decided to add their own improvements to the design when they were finished</text>
			<source>Interlude 12</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Reveller</name>
		<hp>2</hp>
		<type>Thug</type>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<text><p>When this card would be placed in the villain trash or the villain deck, shuffle it into the Thug deck instead.</p><p>At the end of the villain turn, this card deals 1 melee damage to the hero target with the highest HP</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>Countless Merchants had gathered, some perching on piles of trash or rubble as lookouts, and it seemed like everyone was striving to be heard over the music that blared from the countless speakers that were set up in and around the mall.</text>
			<source>Infestation 11.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Tough</name>
		<hp>2</hp>
		<type>Thug</type>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<text><p>When this card would be placed in the villain trash or the villain deck, shuffle it into the Thug deck instead.</p><p>At the end of the villain turn, this card deals 2 melee damage to the 2 hero targets with the highest HP</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>One of the Merchants in the ring had just bludgeoned someone with a length of pipe.</text>
			<source>Infestation 11.6</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Sadist</name>
		<hp>2</hp>
		<type>Thug</type>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<text><p>When this card would be placed in the villain trash or the villain deck, shuffle it into the Thug deck instead.</p><p>At the end of the villain turn, this card deals 2 melee damage to the hero target with the lowest HP</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>Inspired by this sight, a man who stood outside the ring grabbed a piece of rubble and threw it down at the edge of the ring. The chunk of concrete flew into the massed people, striking a man who was crouching and trying to avoid the worst of the fighting.</text>
			<source>Infestation 11.6</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
</deck>