<?xml version="1.0"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="villain_convert.xslt"?>

<deck>
	<name>The Merchants</name>
	<version>1.1</version>
	<villain>
		<name>Skidmark</name>
		<front>
			<title>Superpowered Drug Dealer</title>
			<nemesis>Miss Militia</nemesis>
			<hp>70</hp>
			<setup><small>Place Skidmark in play, "Superpowered Drug Dealer" side up. Search the villain deck for all Thug cards; put them aside as the 'Thug deck'.</small></setup>
			<gameplay><small>If the Thug deck is empty at the start of the villain turn, the heroes lose the game.<br/>
		At the end of the villain turn, play H - 1 Thugs from the top of the Thug deck.<br/>
		When this target is destroyed, flip it instead</small></gameplay>
		</front>
		<back>
			<title>Defeated Drug Dealer</title>
			<gameplay>If the Thug deck is empty at the start of the villain turn, the heroes lose the game.<br/><br/>
		
		At the end of the villain turn, play 1 Thug from the top of the Thug deck.<br/><br/>
		
		If there are no villain targets in play, the heroes win the game</gameplay>
		</back>
	</villain>
	<card>
		<name>Festival of Blood</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<text>Increase damage dealt by villain targets by 1</text>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Festival of Excess</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<text>Reduce damage dealt to villain targets by 1</text>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Festival of Love</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<text>At the start of the villain turn, play the top card of the Thug deck</text>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Not Exactly Sanitary</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<text>Whenever a villain target deals non-toxic damage to another target, the villain target deals 1 toxic damage to that target</text>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Squealer</name>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>8</hp>
		<text>Ignore villain targets when determining targeting for damage from environmental cards. At the start of the villain turn, play the top card in the environment deck</text>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Mush</name>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>10</hp>
		<text>This card is immune to melee and projectile damage. At the end of the villain turn, Mush deals 1 melee damage to all hero targets</text>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Scrub</name>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>10</hp>
		<text>At the start of the villain turn, Scrub deals 5 energy damage to all targets (except himself) with a HP evenly divisible by 3</text>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Helicopter</name>
		<type>Device</type>
		<hp>16</hp>
		<text>Skidmark is immune to melee damage. At the end of the villain turn, play the top card of the Thug deck</text>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Reveller</name>
		<hp>2</hp>
		<type>Thug</type>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<text>When this card would be placed in the villain trash or the villain deck, shuffle it into the Thug deck instead.<br/><br/>At the end of the villain turn, this card deals 1 melee damage to the hero target with the highest HP</text>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Tough</name>
		<hp>2</hp>
		<type>Thug</type>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<text>When this card would be placed in the villain trash or the villain deck, shuffle it into the Thug deck instead.<br/><br/>At the end of the villain turn, this card deals 2 melee damage to the 2 hero targets with the highest HP</text>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Sadist</name>
		<hp>2</hp>
		<type>Thug</type>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<text>When this card would be placed in the villain trash or the villain deck, shuffle it into the Thug deck instead.<br/><br/>At the end of the villain turn, this card deals 2 melee damage to the hero target with the lowest HP</text>
	</card>
</deck>