<?xml version="1.0"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="cards.xslt"?>

<!-- LOGO: Stylised 9 -->

<deck>
	<deckname>Slaughterhouse 9</deckname>
	<version>2.0</version>
	<textcolour>black</textcolour>
	<cardcolour>white</cardcolour>
	<boxcolour>white</boxcolour>
	<villain>
		<name>Slaughterhouse 9</name>
		<front>
			<title>Parahuman Murder Squad</title>
			<setup>Search the Villain deck for all Nine cards, shuffle them, and put them under this card as the Nine deck. Put the top H cards from the Nine deck into play</setup>
		<gameplay>Whenever a Nine card would be destroyed, flip it instead. Whenever no villain targets are in play, the heroes win the game</gameplay>
		<advanced>At the end of the villain turn, put the top card of the Nine deck into play</advanced></front>
	</villain>
	
	<specialcard>
		<name>Jack Slash</name>
		<front>
			<nemesis>Skitter</nemesis>
			<hp>26</hp>
			<type>Parahuman</type>
			<type>Nine</type>
			<text><p>The first time an Attack card would enter the trash each turn, this card deals X melee damage to each hero, where X = 2 * the number of powers contolled by that hero.</p><p>The first time a Special card would enter the trash each turn, play the top card of the villain deck</p></text>
		</front>
		<back>
			<type>Parahuman</type>
			<type>Nine</type>
			<text>Whenever a hero uses a power, this card deals that hero 1 melee damage</text>
		</back>
	</specialcard>
	<specialcard>
		<name>Bonesaw</name>
		<front>
			<nemesis>Grue</nemesis>
			<nemesis>Guts &amp; Glory</nemesis>
			<hp>24</hp>
			<type>Parahuman</type>
			<type>Nine</type>
			<text><p>The first time a Defence card would enter the trash each turn, each villain target regains 2 HP.</p><p>The first time a Special card would enter the trash each turn, this card deals 2 toxic damage to all non-villain targets</p></text>
		</front>
		<back>
			<type>Parahuman</type>
			<type>Nine</type>
			<text>At the end of the villain turn, the villain target with the lowest HP regains 1 HP</text>
		</back>
	</specialcard>
	<specialcard>
		<name>Crawler</name>
		<front>
			<nemesis>Guts &amp; Glory</nemesis>
			<hp>30</hp>
			<type>Parahuman</type>
			<type>Nine</type>
			<text><p>Whenever Crawler is dealt damage, he becomes immune to that damage type until the next time he takes damage.</p>
			<p>The first time an Attack card would enter the trash each turn, this card deals 2 toxic damage and 2 melee damage to the non-villain target with the highest HP.</p>
			<p>The first time a Special card would enter the trash each turn, Crawler regains 30 HP</p></text>
		</front>
		<back>
			<type>Parahuman</type>
			<type>Nine</type>
			<text>At the end of the villain turn, this card deals 2 melee damage to the hero target with the lowest HP</text>
		</back>
	</specialcard>
	<specialcard>
		<name>Burnscar</name>
		<front>
			<nemesis>Labyrinth</nemesis>
			<hp>24</hp>
			<type>Parahuman</type>
			<type>Nine</type>
			<text><p>The first time a Special card would enter the trash each turn, destroy all environment cards then Burnscar deals X fire damage to all non-villain targets, where X = 1 + the number of environment cards destroyed in this way</p>
			<p>The first time an Attack card would enter the trash each turn, deal 3 fire damage to the hero target with the lowest HP, and destroy a hero card</p></text>
		</front>
		<back>
			<type>Parahuman</type>
			<type>Nine</type>
			<text>At the end of the villain turn, this card deals 1 fire damage to all non-villain targets</text>
		</back>
	</specialcard>
	<specialcard>
		<name>Mannequin</name>
		<front>
			<nemesis>Armsmaster</nemesis>
			<hp>26</hp>
			<type>Parahuman</type>
			<type>Nine</type>
			<text><p>Reduce damage dealt to Mannequin by 1.</p>
			<p>The first time a Defence card would enter the trash each turn, destroy 1 hero Ongoing or Equipment card</p></text>
		</front>
		<back>
			<type>Parahuman</type>
			<type>Nine</type>
			<text>Reduce damage dealt to the villain target with the lowest HP by 1</text>
		</back>
	</specialcard>
	<specialcard>
		<name>Shatterbird</name>
		<front>
			<nemesis>Regent</nemesis>
			<hp>24</hp>
			<type>Parahuman</type>
			<type>Nine</type>
			<text><p>The first time an Attack card would enter the trash each turn, Shatterbird deals 2 projectile damage to the H - 1 hero targets with the highest HP</p></text>
		</front>
		<back>
			<type>Parahuman</type>
			<type>Nine</type>
			<text>At the end of the villain turn this card deals 1 projectile damage to all non-villain targets</text>
		</back>
	</specialcard>
	<specialcard>
		<name>Siberian</name>
		<front>
			<nemesis>Bitch</nemesis>
			<hp>26</hp>
			<type>Parahuman</type>
			<type>Nine</type>
			<text><p>The Nine target played just before and just after the Siberian are immune to damage</p></text>
		</front>
		<back>
			<type>Parahuman</type>
			<type>Nine</type>
			<text>The villain target with the lowest HP is immune to melee damage</text>
		</back>
	</specialcard>
	<specialcard>
		<name>Cherish</name>
		<front>
			<nemesis>Regent</nemesis>
			<hp>24</hp>
			<type>Parahuman</type>
			<type>Nine</type>
			<text><p>The first time a Defence card would enter the trash each turn, the hero with the most cards in hand discards 2 cards.</p>
			<p>Whenever Cherish is dealt damage, Cherish deals 2 psychic damage to the target that dealt her damage</p></text>
		</front>
		<back>
			<type>Parahuman</type>
			<type>Nine</type>
			<text>Whenever a target is destroyed during a hero's turn, that hero deals themselves 1 psychic damage</text>
		</back>
	</specialcard>
	
	<card>
		<name>Hatchet Face</name>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<hp>8</hp>
		<text>Heroes may not use powers</text>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<quote>
			<text>"He's strong enough to swing that axe through a car, tough enough you could flatten him with a steamroller and he'd get back up when you were done."</text>
			<source>Tattletale, Sting 26.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Murder Rat</name>
		<hp>8</hp>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<type>Parahuman</type>
		<text>At the end of the villain turn, Murder Rat deals 2 melee damage to the hero target with the lowest HP</text>
		<quote>
			<text>She pushed herself free of the vent, lunging, drawing her claws together as if she were diving into water from a height. Her narrow, emaciated body slipped right between the railings of the ascending and descending stairs.</text>
			<source>Sting 26.3</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Spiderbots</name>
		<hp>4</hp>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<type>Device</type>
		<nemesis>Battery</nemesis>
		<text>At the end of the villain turn, deal X melee damage to the hero target with the lowest HP, where X = 1 + the number of Spiderbots in play</text>
		<quote>
			<text>Spidery contraptions of scrap metal, they lacked heads, only consisting of a box half the size of a toaster and spindly legs that moved on hydraulics, each ending in a syringe or scalpel. A dozen of them, climbing onto the walls and floor.</text>
			<source>Interlude 11h</source>
		</quote>
	</card>

	<card>
		<name>They're All Better Now</name>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<type>Defence</type>
		<text>Flip the most recently defeated Nine card; they have 10 HP. If no cards are flipped in this way, play the top card of the villain deck</text>
		<quote>
			<text>Her mind leaped into action, reaching for knowledge she hadn't had earlier in the night, knowledge of how to fix people. She took in details, grasped everything from the amount of blood her mommy had to heart rate and the amount of air she was breathing, just from the clues in how fast the blood flowed and the color of the skin. She knew the order she'd have to fix things.</text>
			<source>Interlude 25</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>The Scream</name>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<type>Attack</type>
		<text>Each hero may destroy any number of Equipment cards. Then, the Nine card with the highest HP deals each hero target X projectile damage, where X = 2 * the number of Equipment cards in play</text>
		<quote>
			<text>It was as though the glass broke in response to some invisible tidal wave, caught in the nonexistent ‘water', carried along, shattering on impacts with surfaces, slashing anything that would cut, piercing deep into any surface soft enough. I could feel it roll past me, south to north.</text>
			<source>Plague 12.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>You've Been Anticipated</name>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<type>Defence</type>
		<text>Each hero discards 2 cards</text>
		<quote>
			<text>I fumbled for the gun, using my bugs to get a sense for where it was. In the same motion that I pointed it, Jack slapped it out of my hand with two slashes of his knife. He was a dozen feet away, but the knife nonetheless connected with my weapon.</text>
			<source>Prey 14.9</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Some Light Entertainment</name>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<type>Attack</type>
		<text>Each villain target in play deals 2 melee damage to the hero target with the highest HP</text>
		<quote>
			<text>If and when the Slaughterhouse Nine do eliminate five of the six candidates, or if any candidates leave the city, the Slaughterhouse Nine are prepared to penalize the city for their failure.</text>
			<source>Snare 13.1</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Legend</name>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Special</type>
		<text>Increase damage dealt by villain cards by 1</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"If you fail in this, I'll kill nine hundred and ninety-nine people in your name. I'll even break my usual rules to get the body count that high, so it's something special, beyond my usual habits. Maybe a bomb, maybe poison. I'll come up with something. I can target the people you love, those you're closest to, people you've affected. Aster there can be the nine hundred and ninety ninth, and you'll be the thousandth. Perfect. Canceling out the impact you've made in the world, it's poetic."</text>
			<source>Jack, Interlude 11b</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Less Than Human</name>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Defence</type>
		<text>Reduce damage dealt to villain targets by 1</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"Why..." Bonesaw spat blood onto the ground. Being impaled in the heart hadn't put her down. "Ow. Bit my tongue. Why don't you come closer, big man? Too scared to come here and finish me off?"</text>
			<source>Interlude 19</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Some More Friends</name>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<text><p>Play the top card of the Nine deck.</p><p>Play the top card of the villain deck</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>He raised one hand, and Burnscar slapped it in a lazy high-five.

				She turned towards us. "There. He just tagged me in. Forfeited his turn."</text>
			<source>Snare 13.3</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Shall We Play a Game?</name>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<type>Special</type>
		<text><p>If Jack Slash is not in play, find Jack Slash in the Nine deck and put him into play.</p><p>Jack Slash deals 2 psychic damage to all hero targets</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>He smiled. These challenges, after all, served as his own carrot.</text>
			<source>Interlude 12</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>Change the Rules</name>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<type>Defence</type>
		<text>Shuffle all Nine targets in play back into the Nine deck. Deal X Nine cards from the top of the Nine deck, where X = 1 + the number of Nine targets that were in play</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"What I don't understand, is why a blank slate like you would default to doing good deeds, rescuing cats from trees. Why not turn to that violence, as our ancestors did? It drove them, just like it drives the basest and most monstrous of our kind."</text>
			<source>Jack, Interlude 26</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<name>We Don't Take Prisoners</name>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Attack</type>
		<text>Whenever a target is destroyed by a villain card, remove it from the game</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"Forgot to turn the music off"</text>
			<source>Bonesaw, Interlude 25</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
</deck>