<?xml version="1.0"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="cards.xslt"?>

<!-- LOGO: Tower -->

<deck
xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xmlns="http://www.jamespicone.name/parahumans"
xs:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../hero.xsd">
	<name>Alexandria</name>
	<version>2.0.0</version>
	<logo>nul</logo>
	<author>James Picone</author>
	<textcolour>black</textcolour>
	<cardcolour>slategrey</cardcolour>
	<boxcolour>lightgrey</boxcolour>
	<charactercard>
		<name>Alexandria</name>
		<front>
			<hp>30</hp>
			<power>
				<name>Eidetic Memory</name>
				<text>You may play a card. Return one of your cards in play to your hand</text>
			</power>
		</front>
		<back>
			<text>
				<ul>
					<li>Select a target. Until the start of your next turn, reduce damage dealt to that target by 1</li>
					<li>One player may search their deck for a card and put it into their hand</li>
					<li>Deal 2 melee damage to a target</li>
				</ul>
			</text>
		</back>
	</charactercard>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<name>Protector</name>
		<text><p>When this card enters play Alexandria regains 2 HP</p>
		<p>At the end of your turn, select a target. Until the start of your next turn, whenever that target would take damage, redirect that damage to Alexandria</p></text>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<class>Limited</class>
		<name>Named After the Library</name>
		<text>
			<p>When this card enters play shuffle your trash into your deck</p>
			<p>Whenever you would draw a card, instead reveal the top 2 cards of your deck, put 1 in your hand, and return the other to the top of your deck</p>
		</text>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<name>Cold Reading</name>
		<text><p>When this card enters play reveal the top 3 cards of the villain deck. Put them back in any order</p>
		<p>At the start of your turn, reveal the top card of the villain deck. Either discard it or return it to the top of the villain deck</p></text>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<name>Invincible</name>
		<text><p>From when this card enters play until the start of your next turn, when Alexandria would take damage you may discard a card. If you do, prevent the damage.</p>
		<p>Reduce damage dealt to Alexandria by 1</p>
		</text>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<name>Hypersonic Flight</name>
		<text><p>After this card is played you may deal 2 damage to a target</p>
		<p>When Alexandria deals damage to a villain target you may destroy an Equipment or Ongoing card</p></text>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<name>Martial Arts</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<text><p>After this card is played you may destroy a non-character card target</p>
		<p>When Alexandria destroys a target select a target. Until the start of your next turn that target cannot deal damage</p></text>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<name>Imperious Demeanour</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<class>Limited</class>
		<text><p>When this card is put into play draw a card</p>
		<p>Whenever you use a power, Alexandria regains 3 HP</p></text>
	</card>
	<!--(22)-->
	
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<name>Alexandria's Cape</name>
		<text>
			<p>Treat Alexandria as if she was the the target with the highest HP</p>
			<p>Whenever Alexandria would be dealt exactly 1 damage, prevent it</p>
		</text>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<name>Prosthetic Eye</name>
		<text><p>At the end of your turn, reveal the top 3 cards of a deck. Put them back in any order.</p></text>
	</card>
	<!--(4)-->
	
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<name>Time-Locked</name>
		<text><p>Note down Alexandria's current HP</p>
		<p>At the start of your next turn, if Alexandria was not incapacitated, set Alexandria's HP to the value you noted down</p></text>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<name>Pure Strength</name>
		<text>Deal a target 4 melee damage</text>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<name>I Know Them</name>
		<text>Deal 5 damage to the villain target with the highest HP</text>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<name>...And They Know Me</name>
		<text><p>The villain target with the highest HP deals Alexandria 5 psychic damage.</p>
		<p>The villain target with the highest HP cannot deal damage until the start of your next turn</p></text>
	</card>
	<!--(14)-->
	
	
		
	<!--
		Mechanics:
			- Tanking?
			- Melee damage
			- Damage prevention
			- Taking damage for people?
			- Personal deck search
			- Deck manipulation
	-->
</deck>