<?xml version="1.0"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="cards.xslt"?>

<!-- LOGO: Gear -->

<deck
xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xmlns="http://www.jamespicone.name/parahumans"
xs:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../hero.xsd">
	<name>Armsmaster</name>
	<version>2.0.0</version>
	<logo>Armsmaster.svg</logo>
	<author>James Picone</author>
	<textcolour>black</textcolour>
	<cardcolour>midnightblue</cardcolour>
	<boxcolour>mediumaquamarine</boxcolour>
	<charactercard>
		<name>Armsmaster</name>
		<front>
			<hp>30</hp>
			<power>
				<name>Tinker</name>
				<text>Activate a Halberd</text>
			</power>
		</front>
		<back>
			<text>
			<ul>
				<li>One hero regains 2 HP.</li>
				<li>Deal 1 irreducible melee damage to a target.</li>
				<li>One player may search their trash for an Equipment card and put it in their hand.</li>
			</ul>
			</text>
		</back>
		<tags>
			<tag>Character</tag>
			<tag>Hero</tag>
		</tags>
	</charactercard>
	<charactercard>
		<name>Defiant</name>
		<front>
			<hp>28</hp>
			<text><p>Modules may be attached to Defiant, either on the left or right side</p><p>Modules may not be attached to Halberds.</p><p>When a module is attached to Defiant reduce Defiant's maximum HP and current HP by 2.</p></text>
			<power>
				<name>Cyborg</name>
				<text><p>You may activate the primary text of a module attached on the left of Defiant.</p><p>You may activate the secondary text of a module attached on the right of Defiant</p></text>
			</power>

			<power>
				<name>Tinker</name>
				<text>Activate a Halberd</text>
			</power>
		</front>
		<back>
			<text>
				<ul>
					<li>Select a hero target. Reduce the next damage dealt to that target by 2</li>
					<li>Deal 1 lightning damage to all villain targets</li>
					<li>One hero may play an Equipment card</li>
				</ul>
			</text>
		</back>
	</charactercard>
	<charactercard>
		<name>Armmaster</name>
		<front>
			<hp>26</hp>
			<text><p>When a Halberd would enter play, return any other Halberds, and the modules attached to them, to your hand</p></text>
			<power>
				<name>Short-Handed</name>
				<text><p>Put a Halberd into play from your hand</p><p>You may put a Module into play from your hand</p><p>You may activate a Halberd</p></text>
			</power>
			
			<power>
				<name>Humility</name>
				<text><p>Destroy a Halberd. If you do, another player may draw 2 cards</p></text>
			</power>
		</front>
		<back>
			<text>
				<ul>
					<li>A player may draw a card</li>
					<li>Put the top card of a player's deck into play</li>
					<li>Destroy all but one card from each deck</li>
				</ul>
			</text>
		</back>
	</charactercard>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Halberd</type>
		<name>Original Halberd</name>
		<ability>
			<title>Activate</title>
			<text>
				<p>Armsmaster deals 2 melee damage to a target.</p>
				<p>You may activate the primary text of a Module attached on the left of this Halberd.</p><p>You may activate the secondary text of a Module attached on the right of this Halberd</p>
			</text>
		</ability>
		<text>Modules may be attached to this card, either on the left or right side, but only if there isn't already a module attached on that side</text>
		<quote><text>His trademark and weapon was his Halberd, which was basically a spear with an axe head on the end, souped up with gadgets and the kind of technology you generally only saw in science fiction</text><source>Gestation 1.6</source></quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Halberd</type>
		<name>Survey Halberd</name>
		<ability>
			<title>Activate</title>
			<text><p>Draw a card</p><p>You may activate the primary text of a Module on the left of this Halberd.</p><p>You may activate the secondary text of a Module on the right of this Halberd</p></text>
		</ability>
		<text>Modules may be attached to this card, either on the left or right side, but only if there isn't already a module attached on that side</text>
		<quote><text>"Let's see... to deal with my buddy Grue, you've made that thing a fancy tuning stick. Sensing vibrations in the air, translating them into images with that fancy helm of yours?"</text><source>Tattletale, Tangle 6.6</source></quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Halberd</type>
		<name>Experimental Halberd</name>
		<ability>
			<title>Activate</title>
			<text>
				<p>Armsmaster deals 1 irreducible energy damage to a target</p>
				<p>You may activate the primary text of a Module attached on the left of this Halberd.</p><p>You may activate the secondary text of a Module attached on the right of this Halberd</p>
			</text>
		</ability>
		<text>Modules may be attached to this card, either on the left or right side, but only if there isn't already a module attached on that side</text>
		<quote><text>...a dull stainless steel from tip to butt end, with no decoration or style to it. The head was surrounded by a strange blur that seemed static, unmoving around the blade and point</text><source>Extermination 8.4</source></quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Halberd</type>
		<name>Grapple Halberd</name>
		<ability>
			<title>Activate</title>
			<text>
				<p>You may destroy an environment card</p>
				<p>You may activate the primary text of a Module attached on the left of this Halberd.</p><p>You may activate the secondary text of a Module attached on the right of this Halberd</p>
			</text>
		</ability>
		<text>Modules may be attached to this card, either on the left or right side, but only if there isn't already a module attached on that side</text>
		<quote><text>It looked as though he flew up onto the roof, but the six-foot long weapon the man held kind of jerked as he landed. I was pretty sure I saw the tines of a grappling hook retreating back into the end of the weapon.</text><source>Gestation 1.6</source></quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<name>Return in a Flash</name>
		<text>Reveal cards from the top of your deck or your trash until you reveal a Halberd. Either put it into play or into your hand. Return the other cards and shuffle your deck.</text>
		<quote><text>As if to demonstrate, he threw his Halberd straight up in the air. It disappeared into a storm of glowing blue lines as it reached the peak of its ascent, simultaneously rematerializing in his hand.</text><source>Tangle 6.7</source></quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<name>Equipment Stash</name>
		<text>Search your deck for an Equipment card and either put it into play or into your hand. Shuffle your deck</text>
		<quote><text>She stepped into the room. It fell somewhere between a workshop and an office. Two spare suits stood at one side of the room, each with minor functional differences. A set of Halberds were placed on a rack behind Armsmaster's desk, one shattered in pieces. One of the spaces on the rack was empty – Armsmaster had the Halberd in front of him.</text><source>Interlude 7</source></quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<name>Dual-Wielding</name>
		<text>Activate a Halberd</text>
		<quote><text>I saw Armsmaster fighting toe to toe with Leviathan, a Halberd in each hand.</text><source>Extermination 8.4</source></quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<name>Quick Adjustment</name>
		<power>Return a Module in play to your hand. You may play a Module</power>
		<text>Whenever an Equipment card would be destroyed, you may destroy this card instead</text>
		<quote><text>"Ear buds," Tattletale sighed, "Armsmaster told him to wear ear buds, so Dauntless can't hear anyone but him. That's both brilliant and incredibly depressing."</text><source>Tattletale, Tangle 6.7</source></quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Module</type>
		<name>Flamethrower</name>
		<ability>
			<title>Primary</title>
			<text>Deal 2 fire damage to a non-hero target</text>
		</ability>
		<ability>
			<title>Secondary</title>
			<text>Destroy an Environment card</text>
		</ability>
		<text>Attach this card to a Halberd</text>
		<quote><text>The system used light for its circuits, rather than electricity, and it generated a lot of heat as a byproduct</text><source>Teneral e.3</source></quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Module</type>
		<name>Combat Prediction Array</name>
		<ability>
			<title>Primary</title>
			<text>Reveal the top 3 cards of the villain deck, and put them back in any order</text>
		</ability>
		<ability>
			<title>Secondary</title>
			<text>Until the start of your next turn, reduce damage dealt to Armsmaster by villain cards by 1</text>
		</ability>
		<text>Attach this card to a Halberd</text>
		<quote><text>"I've got a computer on my back that's relaying to a supernetwork, noting your every move, using subsonic pulses to read every aspect of the street, the surrounding buildings, every feature of the terrain. I know exactly what you're going to do next – you're going to try to catch me from behind with a wave."</text><source>Armsmaster, Extermination 8.4</source></quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Module</type>
		<name>Recycler</name>
		<ability>
			<title>Primary</title>
			<text>Draw a card</text>
		</ability>
		<ability>
			<title>Secondary</title>
			<text>Activate the secondary text of a Module attached on the left of the card this card is attached to</text>
		</ability>
		<text>Attach this card to a Halberd</text>
		<quote><text>Efficiency, detail and effective use of waste were critical aspects of his particular brand of tinkering</text><source>Teneral e.3</source></quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Module</type>
		<name>Medicator</name>
		<ability>
			<title>Primary</title>
			<text>All hero targets regain 1 HP</text>
		</ability>
		<ability>
			<title>Secondary</title>
			<text>Armsmaster regains 2 HP</text>
		</ability>
		<text>Attach this card to a Halberd</text>
		<quote><text>"I didn't dose him with enough venom to kill him. What I think is that the tranquilizers that you pumped into his system knocked out his ability to heal, which is what let the poisons do as much damage as they did."</text><source>Skitter, Agitation 3.5</source></quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Module</type>
		<name>Grappling Hook</name>
		<ability>
			<title>Primary</title>
			<text>Deal 1 projectile damage to up to 2 non-hero targets</text>
		</ability>
		<ability>
			<title>Secondary</title>
			<text>Destroy an Ongoing card</text>
		</ability>
		<text>Attach this card to a Halberd</text>
		<quote><text>The ball came flying out of the end of his weapon, but my attempt to dodge did little good. He whipped the chain to shift the sphere's trajectory, and simultaneously opened it into its oversized grappling hook form.</text><source>Tangle 6.6</source></quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Module</type>
		<name>Accelerator</name>
		<ability>
			<title>Primary</title>
			<text>All heroes may draw a card</text>
		</ability>
		<ability>
			<title>Secondary</title>
			<text>A hero other than Armsmaster may play a card</text>
		</ability>
		<text>Attach this card to a Halberd</text>
		<quote><text>"Let's see how quickly you respond to classical conditioning. Every time you try to run, I'll do something like that."</text><source>Armsmaster, Extermination 8.4</source></quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Module</type>
		<name>Stasis Effector</name>
		<ability>
			<title>Primary</title>
			<text>Discard 2 cards. If you do, the next time a villain card would be played, put it in the villain trash instead, and until the start of your next turn all villain character cards are immune to damage</text>
		</ability>
		<ability>
			<title>Secondary</title>
			<text>Destroy a target with 4 HP or less</text>
		</ability>
		<text>Attach this card to a Halberd</text>
		<quote><text>"For the record, that last trick was a temporal stasis trigger, with thanks owed to the cooperation of a subordinate of mine. Drains my battery reserves, but you don't understand that, do you?"</text><source>Armsmaster, Extermination 8.4</source></quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Module</type>
		<name>Targeting Computer</name>
		<ability>
			<title>Primary</title>
			<text>Select a hero target. The next time that hero target deals damage, increase the damage by 1 and make the damage irreducible</text>
		</ability>
		<ability>
			<title>Secondary</title>
			<text>Select a target. At the start of Armsmaster's next turn, he deals that target 4 projectile damage</text>
		</ability>
		<text>Attach this card to a Halberd</text>
		<quote><text>The lens of his right eye clicked through multiple frequencies and resolutions, until the scene stood out in high detail. The blood shone ultraviolet, and even particles of dust were highlighted.</text><source>Interlude 16</source></quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Module</type>
		<name>Static Field Generator</name>
		<ability>
			<title>Primary</title>
			<text>Deal 2 lightning damage to a target</text>
		</ability>
		<ability>
			<title>Secondary</title>
			<text>Deal 1 lightning damage to all targets with 3 or less HP</text>
		</ability>
		<text>Attach this card to a Halberd</text>
		<quote><text>He slammed his spear against the ground. The entire cafeteria flinched at the crackle of electricity that ripped through the air around him, flowing along exposed pipe and the heating ducts in a path to the door. Every bug in the hallway died.</text><source>Chrysalis 20.5</source></quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Module</type>
		<name>Communicator</name>
		<ability>
			<title>Primary</title>
			<text>A hero other than Armsmaster may use a power</text>
		</ability>
		<ability>
			<title>Secondary</title>
			<text>A hero other than Armsmaster may play a card</text>
		</ability>
		<text>Attach this card to a Halberd</text>
		<quote><text>They could communicate without talking. Some kind of system built into their masks. It made this harder. I couldn't listen in and anticipate what they were saying.</text><source>Cell 22.5</source></quote>
	</card>
</deck>