<?xml version="1.0"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="cards.xslt"?>

<!-- LOGO: Bared teeth -->

<deck>
	<deckname>Bitch</deckname>
	<version>1.0.0</version>
	<textcolour>black</textcolour>
	<cardcolour>sienna</cardcolour>
	<boxcolour>white</boxcolour>
	<charactercard>
		<name>Bitch</name>
		<front>
			<hp>28</hp>
			<power>
				<name>Attack!</name>
				<text>Each Dog in play may deal 2 melee damage to a target</text>
			</power>
		</front>
		<back>
			<text>
			<ul>
				<li>One target regains 2 HP</li>
				<li>One player may take a card from their trash into their hand</li>
				<li>Reduce damage dealt by environment targets by 2 until the start of your next turn</li>
			</ul>
			</text>
		</back>
	</charactercard>
	
	<charactercard>
		<name>Wag the Dog</name>
		<front>
			<hp>30</hp>
			<power>
				<name>Companionship</name>
				<text><p>Each Dog in play regains 2 HP.</p>
				<p>You may either draw a card, or have a single Dog in play deal 2 melee damage to a target</p></text>
			</power>
		</front>
		<back>
			<text>
			<ul>
				<li>One target regains 2 HP</li>
				<li>One player may take a card from their trash into their hand</li>
				<li>Reduce damage dealt by environment targets by 2 until the start of your next turn</li>
			</ul>
			</text>
		</back>
	</charactercard>
	<card>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<type>Order</type>
		<name>Heel!</name>
		<text><p>Reveal cards from the top of either your deck or your trash until you reveal a Dog. Put it into play. Return the other cards and shuffle your deck.</p><p>Draw a card</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>A whistle. Brutus' ears perk up. Already jumping off the bed as second whistle comes, just after the first. Two whistles like that means come. Master only asks for dogs to come to the front stairs if it is time for walkies!</text>
			<source>Interlude 4</source>
		</quote>
	</card>	
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<type>Order</type>
		<name>Find!</name>
		<text>Reveal the top X cards of a deck, where X = the number of Dog cards in play + 2. For each target revealed in this way, either discard it or put it into play. Shuffle the other cards back into the deck</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"Find her!" she shouted. "Find Skitter! Hurt! Kill!"</text>
			<source>Bitch, Monarch 16.12</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<type>Order</type>
		<name>Guard!</name>
		<text><p>Select up to X targets, where X = the number of Dog cards in play. Reduce damage dealt to those targets by 2 until the start of your next turn.</p><p>Draw a card</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>"Sirius, guard!" she pointed toward the front door of the building. "Bentley! Guard!"</text>
			<source>Bitch, Interlude 11a</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<type>Order</type>
		<name>Hold!</name>
		<text><p>Destroy a target with up to X HP, where X = the number of Dog cards in play * 2.</p><p>Draw a card.</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>The dog lurched forward and placed both front paws on Mannequin's body, pinning his arm and chest.</text>
			<source>Snare 13.3</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<type>Order</type>
		<name>Kill!</name>
		<text>Deal a target X melee damage, where X = the number of Dog cards in play * 3</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"Kill him! Kill!"</text>
			<source>Bitch, Extermination 8.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<type>Order</type>
		<name>Fetch!</name>
		<text>Reveal the top X cards of a deck, where X = the number of Dog cards in play + 2. For each equipment or device card revealed in this way, either discard it or put it into play. Shuffle the other cards back into the deck</text>
		<quote>
			<text>If only humans were as reliable, as easy to train.</text>
			<source>Interlude 11a</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<name>Veterinary Care</name>
		<text><p>Restore all Dog cards to maximum HP.</p><p>You may draw a card.</p><p>You may play a card</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>"Heartworms have a bacteria inside them. When they die, the bacteria gets released into the dog. Having a vet treat it is a long process that involves injecting arsenic into muscles and lots of antibiotics. Like this, his body won't just kill them, but it can kill the disease. He'll be fine by tomorrow."</text>
			<source>Bitch, Buzz 7.2</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<class>Limited</class>
		<name>Whistle</name>
		<text>
			<p>At the start of your turn you may draw a card</p>
			<p>At the end of your turn you may play an Order card</p>
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>Bitch slipped past the pair of them, reaching the front door. I could hear her whistle at a volume that I doubted I could scream.</text>
			<source>Parasite 10.3</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<class>Limited</class>
		<name>The Hunt</name>
		<text>At the start of your turn, each Dog in play may deal 1 melee damage to a target</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"If I ordered them to kill you, Brutus would have torn out your throat before you could scream. I gave them the hurt command."</text>
			<source>Bitch, Insinuation 2.8</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<class>Limited</class>
		<name>Have a Ride</name>
		<text>Reduce damage dealt to hero targets by environment cards by 1</text>
		<quote>
			<text>Leaping from rooftop to rooftop was not as awesome or efficient as it was on TV and in the movies. Even if it was the dogs doing the brunt of the work, they weren't the most graceful of creatures, they weren't built to be ridden, and we didn't have any saddles.</text>
			<source>Tangle 6.7</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<type>Dog</type>
		<hp>6</hp>
		<name>Judas</name>
		<text>At the end of your turn this card deals itself 1 psychic damage</text>
		<quote>
			<text>Judas leaped, nearly twice as far and high as I might have guessed something as big as he was could. The dog's prehensile tail wrapped around Aegis' torso.</text>
			<source>Agitation 3.9</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<type>Dog</type>
		<hp>6</hp>
		<name>Angelica</name>
		<text>At the end of your turn this card deals itself 1 psychic damage</text>
		<quote>
			<text>Angelica positioned herself between enemy and master, and Glory Girl hit the dog broadside. Angelica barely reacted, turning instead to snap at Glory Girl.</text>
			<source>Interlude 11a</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<type>Dog</type>
		<hp>6</hp>
		<name>Brutus</name>
		<text>At the end of your turn this card deals itself 1 psychic damage</text>
		<quote>
			<text>I think Bitch called this one Brutus. He was the biggest, with the meatiest body, and he had a shorter snout. He'd been the Rottweiler, before.</text>
			<source>Agitation 3.8</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<type>Dog</type>
		<hp>6</hp>
		<name>Kuro</name>
		<text>At the end of your turn this card deals itself 1 psychic damage</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"I want to fuck this bastard up," she said. "Last one killed my dogs. Killed Brutus, Judas, Kuro, Bullet, Milk and Stumpy and Axel and Ginger. When do we attack?"</text>
			<source>Bitch, Crushed 24.1</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<type>Dog</type>
		<hp>6</hp>
		<name>Bullet</name>
		<text>At the end of your turn this card deals itself 1 psychic damage</text>
		<quote>
			<text>Leviathan pulled away, only for a dog to snag his arm, drag him off balance. Another latched on to his elbow, while a third and fourth pounced onto his back, tearing into his spine. More crouched and circled around him, looking for opportunities and places to bite.</text>
			<source>Extermination 8.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<type>Dog</type>
		<hp>6</hp>
		<name>Ginger</name>
		<text>At the end of your turn this card deals itself 1 psychic damage</text>
		<quote>
			<text>KOOROW BULLIT
MILK STUMPY
BROOTUS JOODUS
AXIL GINGIR</text>
			<source>Brockton Bay Endbringer Monument, Extermination 8.8</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<type>Dog</type>
		<hp>6</hp>
		<name>Axel</name>
		<text>At the end of your turn this card deals itself 1 psychic damage</text>
		<quote>
			<text>The size of a van, the 'massive object' was animal rather than vehicle, resembling a cross between a lizard and a tiger, with tangles of muscle and bone where it ought to have skin, scales or fur.</text>
			<source>Gestation 1.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<type>Dog</type>
		<hp>6</hp>
		<name>Milk</name>
		<text>At the end of your turn this card deals itself 1 psychic damage</text>
		<quote>
			<text>When the second door leading further into the building was opened, a tide of dogs nearly bowled us over. I couldn't count them, but there were more than ten, less than twenty. All sorts of breeds, different sizes and shapes.</text>
			<source>Buzz 7.2</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<type>Dog</type>
		<hp>6</hp>
		<name>Stumpy</name>
		<text>At the end of your turn this card deals itself 1 psychic damage</text>
		<quote>
			<text>I fell, and in a heartbeat, the other two dogs – a German Shepherd and a hairless terrier with a missing ear and eye – were on me.</text>
			<source>Insinuation, 2.8</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<type>Dog</type>
		<hp>8</hp>
		<name>Bastard</name>
		<quote>
			<text>She looked down at the wolf pup, who was still struggling to bite at her fingers. She let it go, waited until it tried to attack her again, and pushed it down onto its side once more.

"Little bastard," she smiled.</text>
			<source>Interlude 11a</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
</deck>