<?xml version="1.0"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="cards.xslt"?>

<!-- LOGO: Spear -->

<deck
xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xmlns="http://www.jamespicone.name/parahumans"
xs:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../hero.xsd">
	<name>Dauntless</name>
	<version>2.0.0</version>
	<logo>nul</logo>
	<author>James Picone</author>
	<textcolour>black</textcolour>
	<cardcolour>white</cardcolour>
	<boxcolour>white</boxcolour>
	<charactercard>
		<name>Dauntless</name>
		<front>
			<hp>28</hp>
			<power>
				<name>Arclance</name>
				<text>Deal X energy damage to a target, where X = 1 + the number of Charge cards attached to Dauntless / 2 (round down)</text>
			</power>
		</front>
		<back>
			<text>
			<ul>
				<li>One player may draw a card now</li>
				<li>Reduce all energy damage dealt to hero targets by 1 until your next turn</li>
				<li>Select an equipment card. Until your next turn, it is indestructible</li>
			</ul>
			</text>
		</back>
	</charactercard>
	<charactercard>
		<name>Dauntless, Shatter the Sky</name>
		<front>
			<hp>26</hp>
			<text>
				<p>Charge cards may only be attached to Dauntless</p>
				<p>Multiple Charge cards with the same name may be attached to Dauntless, even if they say otherwise</p>
			</text>
			<power>
				<name>Arclance Evolved</name>
				<text>Deal X energy damage to a target, where X = the number of Charge cards attached to Dauntless</text>
			</power>
		</front>
		<back>
			<text>
				<ul>
					<li>Deal 1 energy damage to a target</li>
					<li>Deal 2 energy damage to a target</li>
					<li>Deal 3 energy damage to a target</li>
				</ul>
			</text>
		</back>
	</charactercard>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class><type>Relic</type>
		<name>Arcshield</name>
		<text>This card is indestructible</text>
		<power>Until the end of your next turn reduce damage dealt to Dauntless by X, where X = 1 + the number of Charge cards attached to this card / 2 (round down)</power>
		<quote>
			<text>He was holding his shield arm up, and it had formed into a bubble-shaped forcefield, extending in a ten foot radius around himself, touching both walls on either side of us.</text>
			<source>Tangle 6.7</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class><type>Relic</type>
		<name>Arcstep</name>
		<text>This card is indestructible</text>
		<power><p>Draw X cards, where X = 1 + the number of Charge cards attached to this card / 2 (round down).</p><p>You may play a card</p></power>
		<quote>
			<text>The shoes were the most recent, things that let him leap tall buildings, stand on air, or teleport in a flash of lighting.</text>
			<source>Cenotaph, Interlude R</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Charge</type>
		<name>Charge</name>
		<text><p>When you play this card either attach it to Dauntless or to one of your Relics.</p><p>This card is indestructible</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>His power let him, according to details he'd leaked when he'd appeared on TV and in magazines, imbue his gear with a little bit of power every day.</text>
			<source>Tangle 6.7</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Charge</type>
		<name>Plasma Core</name>
		<text>When you play this card either attach it to Dauntless or to one of your Relics, but only if they do not already have a card with the same name next to them.
			<ul>
				<li>If attached to Dauntless, his Arclance does irreducible damage.</li>
				<li>If attached to the Arcshield, whenever a non-hero target would deal damage to Dauntless and it is reduced by the Arcshield's power, Dauntless deals that target 1 energy damage.</li>
				<li>If attached to the Arcstep, Dauntless regains 1 HP whenever he uses the Arcstep's power</li>
			</ul>
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>...it was a tool with which he could manipulate patterns of the light that wasn't light, that you could touch...</text>
			<source>Cenotaph, Interlude R</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Charge</type>
		<name>Matter to Energy</name>
		<text>When you play this card either attach it to Dauntless or to one of your Relics, but only if they do not already have a card with the same name next to them.
		<ul>
			<li>If attached to Dauntless, you may choose what damage type his Arclance does when it is used.</li>
			<li>If attached to the Arcshield, when its power is used, pick an energy type. Until the end of your next turn, reduce all damage of that type by 1.</li>
			<li>If attached to the Arcstep, when its power is used, Dauntless deals up to 3 targets 1 energy damage</li>
		</ul>
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>...something that served as energy or matter as he chose</text>
			<source>Cenotaph, Interlude R</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<name>To Me!</name>
		<text><p>Search your deck for a Relic and put it into play. Shuffle your deck.</p><p>Draw a card. You may play a card</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>A thought, a crackling flash of white absence, and he was clothed in his armor, spear and shield in his left hand.</text>
			<source>Cenotaph, Interlude R</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<name>Outfitting</name>
		<text>Select a hero. That hero reveals cards from the top of their deck until they reveal an Equipment card. They may put that card into play or into their hand. Shuffle the other revealed cards back into their deck</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"Ear buds," Tattletale sighed, "Armsmaster told him to wear ear buds, so Dauntless can't hear anyone but him. That's both brilliant and incredibly depressing."</text>
			<source>Tattletale, Tangle 6.7</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<name>Resolve</name>
		<text>Reveal cards from the top of your trash or the top of your deck until you reveal a Charge card. You may put it into play or into your hand. If you chose your deck, shuffle the other revealed cards back into your deck</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"I'll just have to do my best."</text>
			<source>Dauntless, Interlude R</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<name>Your Opponent Is Me</name>
		<text>Dauntless deals 2 energy damage to up to 2 targets. Until the start of your next turn whenever those targets would deal damage, redirect that damage to Dauntless</text>
		<quote>
			<text>We'd just crossed the threshold of the parking garage when Dauntless opened fire, striking Brutus no less than three times with jabs of his Arclance, then turning his attention to Angelica.</text>
			<source>Tangle 6.7</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<name>Heroic Image</name>
		<text><p>Whenever Dauntless would be dealt exactly 1 damage prevent that damage.</p><p>Whenever one of Dauntless' cards would be destroyed, Dauntless may destroy this card instead</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>It was expected that he would eventually surpass even the likes of Alexandria, Legend and Eidolon, the 'triumvirate' of the Protectorate, the top dogs. That kind of made him a big deal in Brockton Bay, a hometown hero.</text>
			<source>Tangle 6.7</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<name>Glorious Stand</name>
		<text><p>Whenever a hero target would be damaged, redirect the damage to Dauntless.</p><p>At the start of your turn, destroy this card</p></text>
		<quote>
			<text>In the center of the ring, an oval shape sat embedded in the ground. This was the area where we'd fought Leviathan. A time-distortion grenade had gone off, and three heroes had been trapped inside. Brockton Bay's own Dauntless among them.</text>
			<source>Imago 21.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<name>Crackling Corona</name>
		<text>Whenever a non-hero target causes a hero to discard cards, Dauntless may destroy this card to prevent that hero discarding any cards</text>
		<quote>
			<text>Another thought, directed at his shield, and arcs of white lightning surrounded his body.</text>
			<source>Cenotaph, Interlude R</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<class>Limited</class>
		<name>Carry the Charge</name>
		<text>Whenever Dauntless is dealt energy damage, you may play a card</text>
		<quote>
			<text>He'd tried to explain, how it wasn't about making a taser, how there were these threads that weren't threads, and some he could thicken and others tweak</text>
			<source>Cenotaph, Interlude R</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
</deck>