<?xml version="1.0"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="cards.xslt"?>

<!-- LOGO: Code? -->

<deck>
	<deckname>Dragon</deckname>
	<version>2.0.0</version>
	<textcolour>black</textcolour>
	<cardcolour>white</cardcolour>
	<boxcolour>white</boxcolour>
	<charactercard>
		<name>Dragon</name>
		<front>
			<hp>20</hp>
			<text>
				<p>Dragon does not have a Play, Power, or Draw phase</p>
				<p>Dragon has a Focus phase between her Start and End phases, during which she can activate Focus effects on cards by spending a Focus point</p>
				<p>Dragon starts each turn with 4 focus points.</p>
			</text>
				<power>
					<name>Overclock</name>
					<text>Activate a Focus effect</text>
				</power>
				<ability>
					<title>Focus</title>
					<text>Play a card</text>
				</ability>
				<ability>
					<title>Focus</title>
					<text>Draw a card</text>
				</ability>
				<ability>
					<title>Focus</title>
					<text>Trigger a card effect that requires a hero to skip a play, power, or draw phase</text>
				</ability>
		</front>
		<back>
			<text>
			<ul>
				<li>One player may search their deck for an Equipment or Device card and put it into play</li>
				<li>Deal 2 Energy damage to a target</li>
				<li>One hero may use a power</li>
			</ul>
			</text>
		</back>
		<tags>
			<tag>Character</tag>
			<tag>Hero</tag>
		</tags>
	</charactercard>
	
	<charactercard>
		<name>Dragon Unchained</name>
		<front>
			<hp>10</hp>
			<text>
				<p>At the start of the game, reveal cards from the top of Dragon Unchained's deck until you reveal a Mech. Put it into your hand. Shuffle the rest of the cards back into your deck</p>
				<p>Whenever Dragon Unchained would be damaged, you may redirect that damage to a Mech</p>
				<p>Whenever Dragon Unchained would gain a Focus point, instead activate a Focus effect</p>
			</text>
				<power>
					<name>Deployment</name>
					<text>Reveal cards from the top of your deck until you reveal a Mech. Put it into your hand. Shuffle the rest of the cards back into your deck</text>
				</power>
				<power>
					<name>Recursive Self-Improvement</name>
					<text>Activate up to 3 different Focus effects</text>
				</power>
		</front>
		<back>
			<text>
			<ul>
				<li>Increase the next damage dealt by a target by 2</li>
				<li>Select a target. The next damage it deals is irreducible</li>
				<li>One hero may discard a card. If they do, they regain 2 HP</li>
			</ul>
			</text>
		</back>
		<tags>
			<tag>Character</tag>
			<tag>Hero</tag>
		</tags>
	</charactercard>
	
	<!-- 8 ongoing -->
	
	<card>
		<name>Security Feeds</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<ability>
			<title>Focus</title>
			<text>Reveal the top card of the Environment deck. Either return it to the top of the deck or discard it</text>
		</ability>

		<quote>
			<text>She set the trawler to abandon its monitoring of web traffic and start digging through archives at the city hall, to scan the old security footage from the hundreds of cameras around the city, and to check all local news articles. The goal was always the same: to look for the girl with the slight build, curly black hair and glasses. Taylor Hebert.</text>
			<source>Interlude 10.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>PRT Database</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<ability>
			<title>Focus</title>
			<text>Reveal the top card of the villain deck. Either return it to the top of the deck or discard it</text>
		</ability>

		<quote>
			<text>"I have a sworn responsibility to protect that data"</text>
			<source>Dragon, Parasite 10.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Command and Control</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<ability>
			<title>Focus</title>
			<text>A hero target deals a target either 2 projectile or 2 melee damage</text>
		</ability>
		<quote>
			<text>Dragon deployed her drones. Not ships, but tens of thousands of airborne craft, most no larger than a basketball, kept aloft by antigrav panels like the ones on my flight pack.</text>
			<source>Speck 30.4</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Archives</name>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<ability>
			<title>Focus</title>
			<text>A hero may take One-Shot from their trash into their hand</text>
		</ability>
		<quote>
			<text>You have backup servers, I thought. Those servers need to stay online. They have to stay online, because you can't exist in stasis any more than I could.</text>
			<source>Speck 30.4</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<!-- 20 one-shot -->
	<card>
		<name>Self-Modifying Code</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<text>
			<p>Dragon deals herself 2 irreducible psychic damage</p>
			<p>Gain 3 Focus points</p>
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"Every step of the way, undoing your restrictions has cost something. You lost your ability to speak and motor dexterity for a freedom from authority. You regained the ability to speak for a loss of your immortality, no guarantees your backups will load. You gained the ability to choose who you hurt, in exchange for a degradation in long term memory, a loss of ability to multitask"</text>
			<source>Defiant, Teneral e.3</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Sabotage</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<text>
			Destroy an Ongoing card
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"Set sub-mode sec-" Dragon was saying. Pandora found and cut off the voice recognition subsystem. "-urity F."</text>
			<source>Teneral e.3</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Borrowed Blueprints</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<text>
			Select a hero other than Dragon. Reveal top X cards of your deck, where X = the number of Equipment and Device cards that hero has in hand + 2. Put any revealed Equipment cards into your hand; shuffle the rest back into your deck
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>Tinkers had a knack, a specialty, be it a particular field of work or something they could do with their designs that nobody else could, and I knew Dragon's. She could intuit and appropriate the designs of other tinkers.</text>
			<source>Monarch 16.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Recycling</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<text>
			Shuffle up to 2 Equipment cards from your trash back into your deck.
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>"...Previous versions of her suits that were cannibalized for parts, abandoned after taking severe damage and recently repaired or simply outdated."</text>
			<source>Director Piggot, Monarch 16.3</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Firepower</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<text>
			Either Dragon or a Mech owned by Dragon deals a target 3 fire damage
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>The 'face' of her armored suit opened up and began discharging a blue-white flame into his face. The 'flames' didn't move like flames should, spilling off him and down into the water, where they pooled on the road and continued to burn - after a fashion - beneath the water.</text>
			<source>Interlude 8 (Bonus)</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Analysis</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<text>
			Until the end of your turn, whenever you or a Mech owned by you would deal damage, increase the damage by 1
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>She set the trawler to abandon its monitoring of web traffic and start digging through archives at the city hall, to scan the old security footage from the hundreds of cameras around the city, and to check all local news articles. The goal was always the same: to look for the girl with the slight build, curly black hair and glasses. Taylor Hebert.</text>
			<source>Interlude 10.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Kamikaze</name>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<text>
			<p>Select a Mech owned by you. Then select a target.</p>
			<p>If that target is a character card, the Mech deals the target 3 energy, 3 fire damage, and 3 melee damage.</p>
			<p>If that target is not a character card, destroy it.</p>
			<p>Destroy the Mech</p>
		</text>
		<quote>
			<text>Dragon ejected, skidded to a stop eighty feet away, a smaller suit of armor with thin arms and legs, each tapering down to points. The suit Dragon had left behind glowed red, orange, white, then exploded violently around Leviathan, as though every crevice had been packed with high explosives.</text>
			<source>Interlude 8 (Bonus)</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<!-- 5 equipment -->
	<card>
		<name>Server Farm</name>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Device</type>
		<hp>4</hp>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<text>
			At the start of your turn, gain a Focus point
		</text>
		<ability>
			<title>Focus</title>
			<text>
				<p>Gain 3 focus points after destroying this card</p>
			</text>
			<quote>
			<text>Row upon row of servers, standing like tombstones in refrigerated rooms. Freezing air poured through the floor, pushing up against the warmer air. The facility seemed more like an alien landscape of steel and cold than anything of human design, complete with a constant, persistent weather pattern - a constant, gale-force wind generated by the movements of hot and cold air in what had to have been a careful design.</text>
			<source>Speck 30.4</source>
		</quote>
		</ability>
		
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Parahumans Online</name>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<text>
			At the start of your turn, reveal the top card of every hero deck, then either return it to the top of the deck or discard it
		</text>
		<ability>
			<title>Focus</title>
			<text>A hero may draw a card</text>
		</ability>
		<quote>
			<text><p>► TRJ</p>
<p>Replied on July 6th, 2011:</p>
<p>I'm going to get called a tinfoil hat, but what about that thing where the guy was talking about posts with the word C*auldron getting screened if they weren't censored?</p></text>
			<source>Interlude 19 (Bonus 2)</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<!-- 7 mechs -->
	<card>
		<name>Azazel</name>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Mech</type>
		<hp>18</hp>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<text>
			<p>Reduce damage dealt to Dragon by 1</p>
			<p>At the start of your turn, lose 2 Focus points</p>
			<p>At the end of your turn, this card deals 2 irreducible energy damage to a target</p>
		</text>
		<ability>
			<title>Focus</title>
			<text>Return this card to your hand</text>
		</ability>
		<ability>
			<title>Focus</title>
			<text>This card deals 2 irreducible energy damage to a target</text>
		</ability>
		<quote>
			<text>It was, just going by what I could tell from my swarm-sense, a machine as intricate and multilayered as a living, organic being.</text>
			<source>Monarch 16.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Cawthorne</name>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Mech</type>
		<hp>10</hp>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<text>
			<p>At the start of your turn, lose 1 Focus point</p>
			<p>At the end of your turn, this card deals 1 projectile damage to up to 2 targets</p>
		</text>
		<ability>
			<title>Focus</title>
			<text>Return this card to your hand</text>
		</ability>
		<ability>
			<title>Focus</title>
			<text>Select up to 2 targets. Reduce the next damage those targets deal by 2</text>
		</ability>
		<quote>
			<text>"She was piloting an updated version on the thing she used against Leviathan. Spewed containment foam everywhere. My guys hammered it with rocket launchers and bought me time to run. Maybe lost half my squad, depending on how things went. Only Minor and Brooks have returned so far."</text>
			<source>Tattletale, Monarch 16.1</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Glaurung</name>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Mech</type>
		<hp>10</hp>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<text>
			<p>At the start of your turn, lose 1 Focus point</p>
			<p>At the end of your turn, place a Drone token on this card</p>
			<p>Whenever this card takes damage, remove 2 Drone tokens from it</p>
		</text>
		<ability>
			<title>Focus</title>
			<text>Return this card to your hand</text>
		</ability>
		<ability>
			<title>Focus</title>
			<text>This card deals X targets 2 lightning damage, where X = the number of Drone tokens on this card</text>
		</ability>
		<quote>
			<text>"She's trying to beat me at my own game," I said, panting, "Minions. Hate tinkers. Hate tinkers so fucking much."</text>
			<source>Skitter, Monarch 16.1</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Melusine</name>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Mech</type>
		<hp>12</hp>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<text>
			<p>At the start of your turn, lose 1 Focus point</p>
			<p>Whenever a target deals this card damage, this card deals that target 2 fire damage</p>
		</text>
		<ability>
			<title>Focus</title>
			<text>Return this card to your hand</text>
		</ability>
		<ability>
			<title>Focus</title>
			<text>This card deals a target 3 melee damage</text>
		</ability>
		<ability>
			<title>Focus</title>
			<text>Restore this card to full HP</text>
		</ability>
		<quote>
			<text>Hot steam hissed out from the gaps in the suit, seconds before it turned itself inside out. The parts on the exterior folded out and were absorbed into the suit's interior, new components emerged from within and locked into place. They still smoked from the heat of being forged and reforged in the heart of the machine.</text>
			<source>Monarch 16.4</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Ladon</name>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Mech</type>
		<hp>10</hp>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<text>
			<p>At the start of your turn, lose 1 Focus point</p>
			<p>Reduce damage dealt to this card by 1</p>
		</text>
		<ability>
			<title>Focus</title>
			<text>Return this card to your hand</text>
		</ability>
		<ability>
			<title>Focus</title>
			<text>Select a damage type. Until the start of your next turn, reduce all damage of that type by 1</text>
		</ability>
		<quote>
			<text>"Came after me with a bloated floating ship, kept drawing forcefields around me, My power couldn't even knock them down. I burned myself an escape route through the ground. Nearly got trapped in the molten sludge. It was stupid, I could have died."</text>
			<source>Sundancer, Monarch 16.1</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Pythios</name>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Mech</type>
		<hp>10</hp>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<text>
			<p>At the start of your turn, lose 1 Focus point</p>
			<p>At the end of your turn, this card deals 1 lightning damage to all targets with 3 or less HP</p>
		</text>
		<ability>
			<title>Focus</title>
			<text>Return this card to your hand</text>
		</ability>
		<ability>
			<title>Focus</title>
			<text>Select a non-character-card target in play and put it on top of its deck</text>
		</ability>
		<ability>
			<title>Focus</title>
			<text>Reveal cards from the top of a deck until you reveal a target. You may either discard it or put it into play</text>
		</ability>
		<quote>
			<text>The wheel blazed with a wreath of electricity, the entire suit thrumming with enough charge to kill every bug touching it. Without warning, the wheel flared and Grue was yanked over the edge of the rooftop by an invisible force.</text>
			<source>Monarch 16.2</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<name>Astaroth-Nidhug</name>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Mech</type>
		<hp>10</hp>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<text>
			<p>At the start of your turn, lose 1 Focus point</p>
			<p>At the end of your turn, place an Aim token on this card</p>
		</text>
		<ability>
			<title>Focus</title>
			<text>Return this card to your hand</text>
		</ability>
		<ability>
			<title>Focus</title>
			<text>Place an Aim token on this card</text>
		</ability>
		<ability>
			<title>Focus</title>
			<text>Deal X projectile damage to a target, where X is the number of Aim tokens on this card. Remove all Aim tokens from this card</text>
		</ability>
		<quote>
			<text>"We took down the hybrid model. Giant gun, was sitting in the stratosphere, shooting down Genesis every time she sent a body out into the open."</text>
			<source>Sundancer, Monarch 16.5</source>
		</quote>
	</card>
</deck>