<?xml version="1.0"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="cards.xslt"?>

<!-- LOGO: Infinity sign? Some kind of temple? Hands in prayer?  -->

<deck>
	<deckname>Eidolon</deckname>
	<version>2.0.0</version>
	<textcolour>black</textcolour>
	<cardcolour>white</cardcolour>
	<boxcolour>white</boxcolour>
	<charactercard>
		<name>Eidolon</name>
		<front>
			<hp>26</hp>
			<power>
				<name>Need</name>
				<text>
					<p>Draw a card</p>
				</text>
			</power>
			
			<text>
				<p>Whenever a Power card enters play, if there are more than 3 Power cards already in play, return one of your Power cards to your hand</p>
				<p>If you use a power on a Power card the same turn it enters play, it from the game</p>
			</text>
		</front>
		<back>
			<text>
			<ul>
				<li>1 player may use a power</li>
				<li>Destroy a target that is not a character card</li>
				<li>Destroy all ongoing cards in play</li>
			</ul>
			</text>
		</back>
	</charactercard>
	
	<charactercard>
		<name>Ignis Fatuus</name>
		<front>
			<hp>28</hp>
			<power>
				<name>Flicker</name>
				<text>
					<p>Reveal the top 5 cards of your deck. Put one of the revealed cards into your hand; shuffle the others back into your deck</p>
				</text>
			</power>
			
			<text>
				<p>Whenever a Power card enters play, you may use a power on that card. Then put the card into your trash</p>
			</text>
		</front>
		<back>
			<text>
			<ul>
				<li>1 player may use a power</li>
				<li>Destroy a target that is not a character card</li>
				<li>Destroy all ongoing cards in play</li>
			</ul>
			</text>
		</back>
	</charactercard>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Dig Deep</name>
		<power>Draw 3 cards</power>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Lightning Links</name>
		<power>If there are exactly 2 non-hero targets in play, deal 4 lightning damage to both of them</power>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Danger Sense</name>
		<power>Reveal the top 5 cards of the villain deck. Put any revealed One-Shot cards back on top in any order. Then put the other cards back on top in any order.</power>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Forcefield</name>
		<text>
			<p>At the end of your turn, put a Power token on this card</p>
			<p>When this card enters play, put a Power token on it</p>
		</text>
		<power>
			<p>Until the start of your next turn, any time damage would be dealt to all targets of a particular type, reduce that damage by X, where X is the number of Power tokens on this card right now.</p>
			<p>Remove all Power tokens from this card</p>
		</power>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Transposition</name>
		<power>Select a damage type. The next time damage of that type would be dealt, redirect it to a target of your choice</power>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Void</name>
		<power>
			<p>Destroy a non-character-card target.</p>
			<p>Put a Vacuum token on this card.</p>
			<p>Deal all targets X sonic damage, where X is the number of Vacuum tokens on this card</p>
		</power>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Power Siphon</name>
		<power>
			<p>Select a card.</p>
			<p>You may move any number of tokens to that card from another card with tokens of the same type</p>
			<p>You may move any number of tokens from that card to another card with tokens of the same type</p>
			<p>You may add or remove 1 token to that card of the same type as a token already on that card. If you do, Eidolon deals himself 2 irreducible psychic damage</p>
		</power>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Cliffs of Another World</name>
		<power>
			<p>Destroy all environment cards. Deal a target X energy damage, where X is the number of cards you just destroyed</p>
		</power>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Dimensional Shift</name>
		
		<power>
			<p>Shuffle a card that has been removed from the game back into its deck</p>
		</power>
		
		<power>
			<p>Select a non-indestructible card that isn't a character card and remove it from the game. Then destroy this card.</p>
		</power>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Gravity</name>
		
		<power>
			<p>Deal 2 energy damage to all targets other than Eidolon</p>
		</power>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Destroy the Indestructible</name>
		<text>
			<p>At the end of your turn, put a Power token on this card</p>
			<p>When this card enters play, put a Power token on it</p>
		</text>
		<power>
			<p>Deal X damage to a target, where X is the number of Power tokens on this card.</p>
			<p>Then remove all Power tokens from this card</p>
		</power>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Stand Among the Clouds</name>
		<power>
			<p>Until the start of your next turn, Environment cards have no text.</p>
		</power>
	</card>
	
	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>A Hundred Other Capes</name>
		<power>
			<p>If there are 4 or more non-hero targets in play, destroy all non-character-card, non-hero targets</p>
		</power>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Draw Worship</name>
		<power>
			<p>Destroy a hero Ongoing card. If you do, destroy up to 2 villain Ongoing, Equipment, or Device cards</p>
		</power>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Detonate</name>
		<power>
			<p>Destroy a hero Equipment card. If you do, you may deal a target 3 melee and 3 fire damage</p>
		</power>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Molecular Brake</name>
		<power>
			<p>Deal 3 cold damage to all non-hero targets.</p>
			<p>Destroy all targets with 2 HP or less</p>
			<p>Skip the next hero turn</p>
		</power>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Pierce Through</name>
		<power>
			<p>Deal 3 projectile damage to a villain target.</p>
			<p>Deal 4 projectile damage to a different villain target.</p>
			<p>Deal 2 projectile damage to a hero target</p>
			<p>Deal 1 projectile damage to a different hero target</p>
		</power>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Control</name>
		<power>
			<p>Deal a hero other than Eidolon 4 psychic damage</p>
			<p>That hero may play a card</p>
			<p>That hero may use a power</p>
			<p>That hero may draw a card</p>
		</power>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Accelerate Time</name>
		<power>
			<p>Play the top card of the villain deck</p>
			<p>Each hero (other than Eidolon) may use a power in turn order</p>
		</power>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Creation</name>
		
		<power>
			<p>Reveal the top 2 cards of every deck, starting from yours and going clockwise</p>
			<p>Put any revealed Equipment or Device cards into play. Discard the rest.</p>
			<p>Play the top card of the villain deck</p>
		</power>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Scatterstate</name>
		
		<power>
			<p>Deal 1 energy damage and 1 melee damage to all non-hero targets</p>
			<p>Until the start of your next turn:
				<ul>
					<li>You take 1 less damage</li>
					<li>If damage would be dealt to all heroes or all hero targets, redirect every instance of the damage to you</li>
				</ul>
			</p>
		</power>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Frozen Fortifications</name>
		
		<power>
			<p>Until the start of your next turn:
				<ul>
					<li>Whenever 2 or less damage would be dealt to a hero target, prevent it</li>
					<li>Whenever 3 or more damage would be dealt to a hero target, stop preventing damage, and deal 2 cold damage to all hero targets</li>
				</ul>
			</p>
		</power>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Psychometry</name>
		
		<power>
			<p>Reveal the top 3 cards of a deck. Put any revealed Ongoing cards into play</p>
		</power>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Lines of Force</name>
		
		<power>
			<p>Rearrange the player order.</p>
			<p>Continue play from the next position, not the hero that would have taken the next turn (e.g. if you were the 3rd player in the turn order, the 4th player in the new turn order takes their turn next)</p>
		</power>
		<power>
			<p>Select a deck. Rearrange the order every card from that deck is considered to have entered play (this will effect the ordering of start of turn and end of turn effects)</p>
		</power>
	</card>

	<card>
		<quantity>1</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<type>Power</type>
		<name>Kinetic Dampener</name>
		<power>
			<p>Until the start of your next turn, all irreducible damage is reducible damage instead</p>
		</power>
	</card>
		
	

</deck>