<?xml version="1.0"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="hero_convert.xslt"?>

<deck>
	<name>Miss Militia</name>
	<version>1.5</version>
	<charactercard>
		<name>Miss Militia</name>
		<front>
			<hp>26</hp>
			<power>
				<name>Armory</name>
				<text>Reveal the top 2 cards of your deck. Put any Weapons revealed into play. Discard the other revealed cards. You may active a power on a Weapon card</text>
			</power>
		</front>
		<back>
			<text>
			<ul>
				<li>Deal 2 projectile damage to a target</li>
				<li>Destroy an Equipment card. If you do, deal 4 projectile damage to a target</li>
				<li>Another hero plays a card</li>
			</ul>
			</text>
		</back>
	</charactercard>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Weapon</type>
		<name>Machete</name>
		<power>Deal 2 melee damage to a non-hero target. If you have used the Submachine Gun power since the start of your last turn, deal 3 melee damage to the same target</power>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Weapon</type>
		<name>Pistol</name>
		<power>Deal 2 projectile damage to a non-hero target. If you have used the Submachine Gun power since the start of your last turn, play a card</power>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Weapon</type>
		<name>Submachine Gun</name>
		<power>Deal 1 projectile damage to up to 3 non-hero targets. If you have used the Machete power since the start of your last turn, destroy an Environment or Ongoing card. If you have used the Rifle power since the start of your last turn, put a non-hero target that is not a character card on top of its deck</power>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<type>Weapon</type>
		<name>Sniper Rifle</name>
		<power>Select a target, (other than the villain target with the highest HP, unless they are the only villain target). At the start of your next turn, deal 4 projectile damage to that target. If you have used the Pistol power since the start of your last turn, draw 2 cards</power>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<name>Overdrive</name>
		<text>You may use as many powers this turn as you have Weapons. At the end of your turn, destroy every Weapon card you have in play</text>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<name>Cover Fire</name>
		<text>Deal 2 projectile damage to a non-hero target. 1 hero target regains 2 HP</text>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<name>Grenade</name>
		<text>Deal 2 fire damage and 2 melee damage to a non-hero target. If you deal any damage in this way, destroy an Ongoing card</text>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<name>I Have More</name>
		<text>Destroy a Weapon card. Destroy up to 2 Ongoing or Environment cards</text>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<name>Hail of Bullets</name>
		<text>Deal 2 projectile damage to all non-hero targets</text>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>2</quantity>
		<class>Equipment</class>
		<class>Limited</class>
		<name>Armour</name>
		<text>The next time Miss Militia would be dealt 5 or more damage from a single source, prevent the damage and destroy this card</text>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<class>Limited</class>
		<name>I Don't Sleep</name>
		<text>At the end of your turn, draw a card</text>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<class>Ongoing</class>
		<name>Nonlethal Measures</name>
		<text>Whenever you destroy a target, you may put the destroyed target on the bottom of its deck and destroy this card instead</text>
	</card>
	<card>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<class>One-Shot</class>
		<name>Weaponry</name>
		<text><small>If you have used the Submachine Gun power since the start of your last turn, until the end of your turn, increase damage you deal by 1<br/>
		If you have used the Machete power since the start of your last turn, deal 1 irreducible melee damage to a non-hero target<br/>
		If you have used the Pistol power since the start of your last turn, draw a card<br/>
		If you have used the Sniper Rifle power since the start of your last turn, destroy a non-hero, non-character-card target</small></text>
	</card>
</deck>